{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00000", "text": "BBC announced 11-10-2023 on 83,6, citing John Doe from New York. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "BBC", "label": "organization", "start": 0, "end": 3}, {"text": "11-10-2023", "label": "date", "start": 14, "end": 24}, {"text": "83,6", "label": "number", "start": 28, "end": 32}, {"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 41, "end": 49}, {"text": "New York", "label": "location", "start": 55, "end": 63}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 0, "document_seed": 1499453183, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"BBC": 1, "11-10-2023": 1, "83,6": 1, "John Doe": 1, "New York": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00001", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 35,8.\nGuest: We measured Northwind Research on the study dated 09/12/2024.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Marcus Chen in December 06, 2019, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "35,8", "label": "number", "start": 48, "end": 52}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 73, "end": 91}, {"text": "09/12/2024", "label": "date", "start": 111, "end": 121}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 163, "end": 174}, {"text": "December 06, 2019", "label": "date", "start": 178, "end": 195}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 1, "document_seed": 465693301, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"35,8": 1, "Northwind Research": 1, "09/12/2024": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1, "December 06, 2019": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00002", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 12/07/2024.\nGuest: We measured 25,0 on the study dated October 17, 2020.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is 10.2 in Northwind Research, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "12/07/2024", "label": "date", "start": 48, "end": 58}, {"text": "25,0", "label": "number", "start": 79, "end": 83}, {"text": "October 17, 2020", "label": "date", "start": 103, "end": 119}, {"text": "10.2", "label": "number", "start": 161, "end": 165}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 169, "end": 187}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 2, "document_seed": 8521178, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"12/07/2024": 1, "25,0": 1, "October 17, 2020": 1, "10.2": 1, "Northwind Research": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00003", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Northwind Research.\nGuest: We measured 57,6 on the study dated 77.8.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Acme Corp in 28-12-2022, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 48, "end": 66}, {"text": "57,6", "label": "number", "start": 87, "end": 91}, {"text": "77.8", "label": "number", "start": 111, "end": 115}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 157, "end": 166}, {"text": "28-12-2022", "label": "date", "start": 170, "end": 180}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 3, "document_seed": 1340969353, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Northwind Research": 1, "57,6": 1, "77.8": 1, "Acme Corp": 1, "28-12-2022": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00004", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 89.7.\nGuest: We measured James Okafor on the study dated Dr. Priya Sharma.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Marcus Chen in 16-05-2025, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "89.7", "label": "number", "start": 48, "end": 52}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 73, "end": 85}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 105, "end": 121}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 163, "end": 174}, {"text": "16-05-2025", "label": "date", "start": 178, "end": 188}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 4, "document_seed": 1437519957, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"89.7": 1, "James Okafor": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1, "16-05-2025": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00005", "text": "Officials in 42.2 said The Guardian would affect May 02, 2024 after Berlin reported Reuters. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "42.2", "label": "number", "start": 13, "end": 17}, {"text": "The Guardian", "label": "organization", "start": 23, "end": 35}, {"text": "May 02, 2024", "label": "date", "start": 49, "end": 61}, {"text": "Berlin", "label": "location", "start": 68, "end": 74}, {"text": "Reuters", "label": "organization", "start": 84, "end": 91}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 5, "document_seed": 1257282031, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"42.2": 1, "The Guardian": 1, "May 02, 2024": 1, "Berlin": 1, "Reuters": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00006", "text": "32.7 announced John Doe on 64, citing London from The Guardian. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "32.7", "label": "number", "start": 0, "end": 4}, {"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 15, "end": 23}, {"text": "64", "label": "number", "start": 27, "end": 29}, {"text": "London", "label": "location", "start": 38, "end": 44}, {"text": "The Guardian", "label": "organization", "start": 50, "end": 62}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 6, "document_seed": 703466448, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"32.7": 1, "John Doe": 1, "64": 1, "London": 1, "The Guardian": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00007", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Marcus Chen.\nGuest: We measured Pelorus Media on the study dated July 24, 2019.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is James Okafor in Northwind Research, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 59}, {"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 80, "end": 93}, {"text": "July 24, 2019", "label": "date", "start": 113, "end": 126}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 168, "end": 180}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 184, "end": 202}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 7, "document_seed": 1495950272, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Marcus Chen": 1, "Pelorus Media": 1, "July 24, 2019": 1, "James Okafor": 1, "Northwind Research": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00008", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 12-07-2025.\nGuest: We measured Dr. Priya Sharma on the study dated 95.10.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Acme Corp in James Okafor, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "12-07-2025", "label": "date", "start": 48, "end": 58}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 79, "end": 95}, {"text": "95.10", "label": "number", "start": 115, "end": 120}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 162, "end": 171}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 175, "end": 187}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 8, "document_seed": 711465565, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"12-07-2025": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "95.10": 1, "Acme Corp": 1, "James Okafor": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00009", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Pelorus Media.\nGuest: We measured 10-08-2026 on the study dated 2,0.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is 18/09/2016 in Acme Corp, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 48, "end": 61}, {"text": "10-08-2026", "label": "date", "start": 82, "end": 92}, {"text": "2,0", "label": "number", "start": 112, "end": 115}, {"text": "18/09/2016", "label": "date", "start": 157, "end": 167}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 171, "end": 180}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 9, "document_seed": 633796018, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Pelorus Media": 1, "10-08-2026": 1, "2,0": 1, "18/09/2016": 1, "Acme Corp": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00010", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 15 Apr 2026.\nGuest: We measured Pelorus Media on the study dated Acme Corp.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is James Okafor in Dr. Priya Sharma, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "15 Apr 2026", "label": "date", "start": 48, "end": 59}, {"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 80, "end": 93}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 113, "end": 122}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 164, "end": 176}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 180, "end": 196}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 10, "document_seed": 429461341, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"15 Apr 2026": 1, "Pelorus Media": 1, "Acme Corp": 1, "James Okafor": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00011", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Elena Volkov.\nGuest: We measured January 14, 2015 on the study dated 20.2.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is James Okafor in Dr. Priya Sharma, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 60}, {"text": "January 14, 2015", "label": "date", "start": 81, "end": 97}, {"text": "20.2", "label": "number", "start": 117, "end": 121}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 163, "end": 175}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 179, "end": 195}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 11, "document_seed": 1700845762, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Elena Volkov": 1, "January 14, 2015": 1, "20.2": 1, "James Okafor": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00012", "text": "I tried Hugging Face with Alex last week and saw Jordan compared to ResNet on Transformer. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility.", "entities": [{"text": "Hugging Face", "label": "organization", "start": 8, "end": 20}, {"text": "Alex", "label": "person", "start": 26, "end": 30}, {"text": "Jordan", "label": "person", "start": 49, "end": 55}, {"text": "ResNet", "label": "model", "start": 68, "end": 74}, {"text": "Transformer", "label": "model", "start": 78, "end": 89}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "blog_post", "document_type": "blog_post", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 12, "document_seed": 1508665573, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Hugging Face": 1, "Alex": 1, "Jordan": 1, "ResNet": 1, "Transformer": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00013", "text": "I tried Sam with Medium last week and saw Transformer compared to Hugging Face on GitHub. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility.", "entities": [{"text": "Sam", "label": "person", "start": 8, "end": 11}, {"text": "Medium", "label": "organization", "start": 17, "end": 23}, {"text": "Transformer", "label": "model", "start": 42, "end": 53}, {"text": "Hugging Face", "label": "organization", "start": 66, "end": 78}, {"text": "GitHub", "label": "organization", "start": 82, "end": 88}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "blog_post", "document_type": "blog_post", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 13, "document_seed": 725988172, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Sam": 1, "Medium": 1, "Transformer": 1, "Hugging Face": 1, "GitHub": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00014", "text": "After reading about attention mechanism, I paired it with GPT-3 and tracked Hugging Face using pre-training in ViT. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility.", "entities": [{"text": "attention mechanism", "label": "method", "start": 20, "end": 39}, {"text": "GPT-3", "label": "model", "start": 58, "end": 63}, {"text": "Hugging Face", "label": "organization", "start": 76, "end": 88}, {"text": "pre-training", "label": "method", "start": 95, "end": 107}, {"text": "ViT", "label": "model", "start": 111, "end": 114}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "blog_post", "document_type": "blog_post", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 14, "document_seed": 1847339663, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"attention mechanism": 1, "GPT-3": 1, "Hugging Face": 1, "pre-training": 1, "ViT": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00015", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Marcus Chen.\nGuest: We measured Northwind Research on the study dated Elena Volkov.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Acme Corp in Dr. Priya Sharma, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 59}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 80, "end": 98}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 118, "end": 130}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 172, "end": 181}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 185, "end": 201}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 15, "document_seed": 1659843538, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Marcus Chen": 1, "Northwind Research": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1, "Acme Corp": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00016", "text": "After reading about Hugging Face, I paired it with fine-tuning and tracked ViT using Medium in Alex. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility.", "entities": [{"text": "Hugging Face", "label": "organization", "start": 20, "end": 32}, {"text": "fine-tuning", "label": "method", "start": 51, "end": 62}, {"text": "ViT", "label": "model", "start": 75, "end": 78}, {"text": "Medium", "label": "organization", "start": 85, "end": 91}, {"text": "Alex", "label": "person", "start": 95, "end": 99}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "blog_post", "document_type": "blog_post", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 16, "document_seed": 1977212501, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Hugging Face": 1, "fine-tuning": 1, "ViT": 1, "Medium": 1, "Alex": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00017", "text": "After reading about GPT-3, I paired it with Sam and tracked ViT using Transformer in Jordan. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility.", "entities": [{"text": "GPT-3", "label": "model", "start": 20, "end": 25}, {"text": "Sam", "label": "person", "start": 44, "end": 47}, {"text": "ViT", "label": "model", "start": 60, "end": 63}, {"text": "Transformer", "label": "model", "start": 70, "end": 81}, {"text": "Jordan", "label": "person", "start": 85, "end": 91}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "blog_post", "document_type": "blog_post", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 17, "document_seed": 2133609986, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"GPT-3": 1, "Sam": 1, "ViT": 1, "Transformer": 1, "Jordan": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00018", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Elena Volkov.\nGuest: We measured Marcus Chen on the study dated 16-09-2020.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is James Okafor in 05/04/2025, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 60}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 81, "end": 92}, {"text": "16-09-2020", "label": "date", "start": 112, "end": 122}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 164, "end": 176}, {"text": "05/04/2025", "label": "date", "start": 180, "end": 190}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 18, "document_seed": 976023075, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Elena Volkov": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1, "16-09-2020": 1, "James Okafor": 1, "05/04/2025": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00019", "text": "Maria Garcia announced 42,5 on 4.3, citing Associated Press from Berlin. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Maria Garcia", "label": "person", "start": 0, "end": 12}, {"text": "42,5", "label": "number", "start": 23, "end": 27}, {"text": "4.3", "label": "number", "start": 31, "end": 34}, {"text": "Associated Press", "label": "organization", "start": 43, "end": 59}, {"text": "Berlin", "label": "location", "start": 65, "end": 71}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 19, "document_seed": 786425518, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Maria Garcia": 1, "42,5": 1, "4.3": 1, "Associated Press": 1, "Berlin": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00020", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Pelorus Media.\nGuest: We measured Elena Volkov on the study dated 25-06-2018.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Dr. Priya Sharma in Acme Corp, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 48, "end": 61}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 82, "end": 94}, {"text": "25-06-2018", "label": "date", "start": 114, "end": 124}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 166, "end": 182}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 186, "end": 195}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 20, "document_seed": 1335012661, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Pelorus Media": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1, "25-06-2018": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "Acme Corp": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00021", "text": "After reading about fine-tuning, I paired it with Transformer and tracked Medium using Alex in Jordan. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility.", "entities": [{"text": "fine-tuning", "label": "method", "start": 20, "end": 31}, {"text": "Transformer", "label": "model", "start": 50, "end": 61}, {"text": "Medium", "label": "organization", "start": 74, "end": 80}, {"text": "Alex", "label": "person", "start": 87, "end": 91}, {"text": "Jordan", "label": "person", "start": 95, "end": 101}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "blog_post", "document_type": "blog_post", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 21, "document_seed": 1077335263, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"fine-tuning": 1, "Transformer": 1, "Medium": 1, "Alex": 1, "Jordan": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00022", "text": "Tokyo announced 81 on The Guardian, citing Jane Smith from 19 Jan 2017. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Tokyo", "label": "location", "start": 0, "end": 5}, {"text": "81", "label": "number", "start": 16, "end": 18}, {"text": "The Guardian", "label": "organization", "start": 22, "end": 34}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 43, "end": 53}, {"text": "19 Jan 2017", "label": "date", "start": 59, "end": 70}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 22, "document_seed": 262679467, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Tokyo": 1, "81": 1, "The Guardian": 1, "Jane Smith": 1, "19 Jan 2017": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00023", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Pelorus Media.\nGuest: We measured Dr. Priya Sharma on the study dated Northwind Research.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Marcus Chen in Elena Volkov, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 48, "end": 61}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 82, "end": 98}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 118, "end": 136}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 178, "end": 189}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 193, "end": 205}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 23, "document_seed": 1405812636, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Pelorus Media": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "Northwind Research": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00024", "text": "I tried ViT with Transformer last week and saw BERT compared to GPT-3 on attention mechanism. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility.", "entities": [{"text": "ViT", "label": "model", "start": 8, "end": 11}, {"text": "Transformer", "label": "model", "start": 17, "end": 28}, {"text": "BERT", "label": "model", "start": 47, "end": 51}, {"text": "GPT-3", "label": "model", "start": 64, "end": 69}, {"text": "attention mechanism", "label": "method", "start": 73, "end": 92}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "blog_post", "document_type": "blog_post", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 24, "document_seed": 500160735, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"ViT": 1, "Transformer": 1, "BERT": 1, "GPT-3": 1, "attention mechanism": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00025", "text": "After reading about GPT-3, I paired it with pre-training and tracked Sam using BERT in Medium. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility.", "entities": [{"text": "GPT-3", "label": "model", "start": 20, "end": 25}, {"text": "pre-training", "label": "method", "start": 44, "end": 56}, {"text": "Sam", "label": "person", "start": 69, "end": 72}, {"text": "BERT", "label": "model", "start": 79, "end": 83}, {"text": "Medium", "label": "organization", "start": 87, "end": 93}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "blog_post", "document_type": "blog_post", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 25, "document_seed": 1538824452, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"GPT-3": 1, "pre-training": 1, "Sam": 1, "BERT": 1, "Medium": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00026", "text": "April 20, 2016 announced Reuters on Associated Press, citing The Guardian from New York. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "April 20, 2016", "label": "date", "start": 0, "end": 14}, {"text": "Reuters", "label": "organization", "start": 25, "end": 32}, {"text": "Associated Press", "label": "organization", "start": 36, "end": 52}, {"text": "The Guardian", "label": "organization", "start": 61, "end": 73}, {"text": "New York", "label": "location", "start": 79, "end": 87}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 26, "document_seed": 797113617, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"April 20, 2016": 1, "Reuters": 1, "Associated Press": 1, "The Guardian": 1, "New York": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00027", "text": "After reading about Medium, I paired it with Alex and tracked Sam using Jordan in fine-tuning. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility.", "entities": [{"text": "Medium", "label": "organization", "start": 20, "end": 26}, {"text": "Alex", "label": "person", "start": 45, "end": 49}, {"text": "Sam", "label": "person", "start": 62, "end": 65}, {"text": "Jordan", "label": "person", "start": 72, "end": 78}, {"text": "fine-tuning", "label": "method", "start": 82, "end": 93}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "blog_post", "document_type": "blog_post", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 27, "document_seed": 1685563731, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Medium": 1, "Alex": 1, "Sam": 1, "Jordan": 1, "fine-tuning": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00028", "text": "71,5 announced March 25, 2020 on Maria Garcia, citing Berlin from 76.10. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "71,5", "label": "number", "start": 0, "end": 4}, {"text": "March 25, 2020", "label": "date", "start": 15, "end": 29}, {"text": "Maria Garcia", "label": "person", "start": 33, "end": 45}, {"text": "Berlin", "label": "location", "start": 54, "end": 60}, {"text": "76.10", "label": "number", "start": 66, "end": 71}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 28, "document_seed": 2105810608, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"71,5": 1, "March 25, 2020": 1, "Maria Garcia": 1, "Berlin": 1, "76.10": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00029", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 12/10/2022.\nGuest: We measured Acme Corp on the study dated 73.3.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Elena Volkov in Northwind Research, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "12/10/2022", "label": "date", "start": 48, "end": 58}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 79, "end": 88}, {"text": "73.3", "label": "number", "start": 108, "end": 112}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 154, "end": 166}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 170, "end": 188}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 29, "document_seed": 1623848309, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"12/10/2022": 1, "Acme Corp": 1, "73.3": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1, "Northwind Research": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00030", "text": "New York announced John Doe on Jane Smith, citing The Guardian from BBC. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "New York", "label": "location", "start": 0, "end": 8}, {"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 19, "end": 27}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 31, "end": 41}, {"text": "The Guardian", "label": "organization", "start": 50, "end": 62}, {"text": "BBC", "label": "organization", "start": 68, "end": 71}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 30, "document_seed": 1239588500, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"New York": 1, "John Doe": 1, "Jane Smith": 1, "The Guardian": 1, "BBC": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00031", "text": "Officials in 59,4 said The Guardian would affect 30 Jul 2022 after 62.2 reported Berlin. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "59,4", "label": "number", "start": 13, "end": 17}, {"text": "The Guardian", "label": "organization", "start": 23, "end": 35}, {"text": "30 Jul 2022", "label": "date", "start": 49, "end": 60}, {"text": "62.2", "label": "number", "start": 67, "end": 71}, {"text": "Berlin", "label": "location", "start": 81, "end": 87}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 31, "document_seed": 533573460, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"59,4": 1, "The Guardian": 1, "30 Jul 2022": 1, "62.2": 1, "Berlin": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00032", "text": "08/04/2023 announced John Doe on 04-02-2020, citing Jane Smith from Maria Garcia. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "08/04/2023", "label": "date", "start": 0, "end": 10}, {"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 21, "end": 29}, {"text": "04-02-2020", "label": "date", "start": 33, "end": 43}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 52, "end": 62}, {"text": "Maria Garcia", "label": "person", "start": 68, "end": 80}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 32, "document_seed": 1799364085, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"08/04/2023": 1, "John Doe": 1, "04-02-2020": 1, "Jane Smith": 1, "Maria Garcia": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00033", "text": "BBC announced 7,8 on Jane Smith, citing Associated Press from The Guardian. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "BBC", "label": "organization", "start": 0, "end": 3}, {"text": "7,8", "label": "number", "start": 14, "end": 17}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 21, "end": 31}, {"text": "Associated Press", "label": "organization", "start": 40, "end": 56}, {"text": "The Guardian", "label": "organization", "start": 62, "end": 74}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 33, "document_seed": 1537058048, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"BBC": 1, "7,8": 1, "Jane Smith": 1, "Associated Press": 1, "The Guardian": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00034", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 77.5.\nGuest: We measured Elena Volkov on the study dated 26-09-2015.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Marcus Chen in Acme Corp, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "77.5", "label": "number", "start": 48, "end": 52}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 73, "end": 85}, {"text": "26-09-2015", "label": "date", "start": 105, "end": 115}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 157, "end": 168}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 172, "end": 181}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 34, "document_seed": 1248452429, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"77.5": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1, "26-09-2015": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1, "Acme Corp": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00035", "text": "After reading about pre-training, I paired it with GitHub and tracked Sam using Hugging Face in Alex. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility.", "entities": [{"text": "pre-training", "label": "method", "start": 20, "end": 32}, {"text": "GitHub", "label": "organization", "start": 51, "end": 57}, {"text": "Sam", "label": "person", "start": 70, "end": 73}, {"text": "Hugging Face", "label": "organization", "start": 80, "end": 92}, {"text": "Alex", "label": "person", "start": 96, "end": 100}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "blog_post", "document_type": "blog_post", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 35, "document_seed": 1127948516, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"pre-training": 1, "GitHub": 1, "Sam": 1, "Hugging Face": 1, "Alex": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00036", "text": "I tried ResNet with Hugging Face last week and saw Alex compared to BERT on Sam. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility.", "entities": [{"text": "ResNet", "label": "model", "start": 8, "end": 14}, {"text": "Hugging Face", "label": "organization", "start": 20, "end": 32}, {"text": "Alex", "label": "person", "start": 51, "end": 55}, {"text": "BERT", "label": "model", "start": 68, "end": 72}, {"text": "Sam", "label": "person", "start": 76, "end": 79}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "blog_post", "document_type": "blog_post", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 36, "document_seed": 545659014, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"ResNet": 1, "Hugging Face": 1, "Alex": 1, "BERT": 1, "Sam": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00037", "text": "John Doe announced The Guardian on February 25, 2016, citing 15 Jan 2018 from BBC. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 0, "end": 8}, {"text": "The Guardian", "label": "organization", "start": 19, "end": 31}, {"text": "February 25, 2016", "label": "date", "start": 35, "end": 52}, {"text": "15 Jan 2018", "label": "date", "start": 61, "end": 72}, {"text": "BBC", "label": "organization", "start": 78, "end": 81}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 37, "document_seed": 474256283, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"John Doe": 1, "The Guardian": 1, "February 25, 2016": 1, "15 Jan 2018": 1, "BBC": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00038", "text": "Maria Garcia announced 05/05/2017 on 05 Jun 2019, citing London from John Doe. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Maria Garcia", "label": "person", "start": 0, "end": 12}, {"text": "05/05/2017", "label": "date", "start": 23, "end": 33}, {"text": "05 Jun 2019", "label": "date", "start": 37, "end": 48}, {"text": "London", "label": "location", "start": 57, "end": 63}, {"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 69, "end": 77}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 38, "document_seed": 2066270234, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Maria Garcia": 1, "05/05/2017": 1, "05 Jun 2019": 1, "London": 1, "John Doe": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00039", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Northwind Research.\nGuest: We measured Dr. Priya Sharma on the study dated Elena Volkov.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Marcus Chen in James Okafor, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 48, "end": 66}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 87, "end": 103}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 123, "end": 135}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 177, "end": 188}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 192, "end": 204}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 39, "document_seed": 1678318293, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Northwind Research": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1, "James Okafor": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00040", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Pelorus Media.\nGuest: We measured Acme Corp on the study dated July 13, 2025.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Elena Volkov in James Okafor, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 48, "end": 61}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 82, "end": 91}, {"text": "July 13, 2025", "label": "date", "start": 111, "end": 124}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 166, "end": 178}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 182, "end": 194}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 40, "document_seed": 1531468518, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Pelorus Media": 1, "Acme Corp": 1, "July 13, 2025": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1, "James Okafor": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00041", "text": "After reading about Jordan, I paired it with Alex and tracked pre-training using Sam in fine-tuning. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility.", "entities": [{"text": "Jordan", "label": "person", "start": 20, "end": 26}, {"text": "Alex", "label": "person", "start": 45, "end": 49}, {"text": "pre-training", "label": "method", "start": 62, "end": 74}, {"text": "Sam", "label": "person", "start": 81, "end": 84}, {"text": "fine-tuning", "label": "method", "start": 88, "end": 99}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "blog_post", "document_type": "blog_post", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 41, "document_seed": 61892133, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Jordan": 1, "Alex": 1, "pre-training": 1, "Sam": 1, "fine-tuning": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00042", "text": "07-12-2018 announced 16/06/2022 on Jane Smith, citing John Doe from June 05, 2024. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "07-12-2018", "label": "date", "start": 0, "end": 10}, {"text": "16/06/2022", "label": "date", "start": 21, "end": 31}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 35, "end": 45}, {"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 54, "end": 62}, {"text": "June 05, 2024", "label": "date", "start": 68, "end": 81}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 42, "document_seed": 821571720, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"07-12-2018": 1, "16/06/2022": 1, "Jane Smith": 1, "John Doe": 1, "June 05, 2024": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00043", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Pelorus Media.\nGuest: We measured Elena Volkov on the study dated 06-12-2021.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Dr. Priya Sharma in 87.7, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 48, "end": 61}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 82, "end": 94}, {"text": "06-12-2021", "label": "date", "start": 114, "end": 124}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 166, "end": 182}, {"text": "87.7", "label": "number", "start": 186, "end": 190}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 43, "document_seed": 874235229, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Pelorus Media": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1, "06-12-2021": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "87.7": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00044", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Marcus Chen.\nGuest: We measured April 10, 2019 on the study dated 81.3.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Dr. Priya Sharma in 68,4, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 59}, {"text": "April 10, 2019", "label": "date", "start": 80, "end": 94}, {"text": "81.3", "label": "number", "start": 114, "end": 118}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 160, "end": 176}, {"text": "68,4", "label": "number", "start": 180, "end": 184}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 44, "document_seed": 245771251, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Marcus Chen": 1, "April 10, 2019": 1, "81.3": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "68,4": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00045", "text": "Officials in BBC said 35,2 would affect London after New York reported May 11, 2026. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "BBC", "label": "organization", "start": 13, "end": 16}, {"text": "35,2", "label": "number", "start": 22, "end": 26}, {"text": "London", "label": "location", "start": 40, "end": 46}, {"text": "New York", "label": "location", "start": 53, "end": 61}, {"text": "May 11, 2026", "label": "date", "start": 71, "end": 83}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 45, "document_seed": 797387223, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"BBC": 1, "35,2": 1, "London": 1, "New York": 1, "May 11, 2026": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00046", "text": "New York announced 25.2 on 26 Apr 2016, citing Berlin from March 11, 2017. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "New York", "label": "location", "start": 0, "end": 8}, {"text": "25.2", "label": "number", "start": 19, "end": 23}, {"text": "26 Apr 2016", "label": "date", "start": 27, "end": 38}, {"text": "Berlin", "label": "location", "start": 47, "end": 53}, {"text": "March 11, 2017", "label": "date", "start": 59, "end": 73}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 46, "document_seed": 1373809046, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"New York": 1, "25.2": 1, "26 Apr 2016": 1, "Berlin": 1, "March 11, 2017": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00047", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 20-12-2026.\nGuest: We measured Pelorus Media on the study dated 29-10-2024.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is 51.2 in Northwind Research, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "20-12-2026", "label": "date", "start": 48, "end": 58}, {"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 79, "end": 92}, {"text": "29-10-2024", "label": "date", "start": 112, "end": 122}, {"text": "51.2", "label": "number", "start": 164, "end": 168}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 172, "end": 190}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 47, "document_seed": 1827288830, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"20-12-2026": 1, "Pelorus Media": 1, "29-10-2024": 1, "51.2": 1, "Northwind Research": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00048", "text": "Tokyo announced Berlin on Associated Press, citing December 28, 2015 from 11,2. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Tokyo", "label": "location", "start": 0, "end": 5}, {"text": "Berlin", "label": "location", "start": 16, "end": 22}, {"text": "Associated Press", "label": "organization", "start": 26, "end": 42}, {"text": "December 28, 2015", "label": "date", "start": 51, "end": 68}, {"text": "11,2", "label": "number", "start": 74, "end": 78}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 48, "document_seed": 1937937627, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Tokyo": 1, "Berlin": 1, "Associated Press": 1, "December 28, 2015": 1, "11,2": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00049", "text": "After reading about BERT, I paired it with Hugging Face and tracked GitHub using fine-tuning in Jordan. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility.", "entities": [{"text": "BERT", "label": "model", "start": 20, "end": 24}, {"text": "Hugging Face", "label": "organization", "start": 43, "end": 55}, {"text": "GitHub", "label": "organization", "start": 68, "end": 74}, {"text": "fine-tuning", "label": "method", "start": 81, "end": 92}, {"text": "Jordan", "label": "person", "start": 96, "end": 102}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "blog_post", "document_type": "blog_post", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 49, "document_seed": 717018060, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"BERT": 1, "Hugging Face": 1, "GitHub": 1, "fine-tuning": 1, "Jordan": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00050", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Dr. Priya Sharma.\nGuest: We measured 37,9 on the study dated Acme Corp.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Northwind Research in 13-02-2025, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 64}, {"text": "37,9", "label": "number", "start": 85, "end": 89}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 109, "end": 118}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 160, "end": 178}, {"text": "13-02-2025", "label": "date", "start": 182, "end": 192}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 50, "document_seed": 139453057, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "37,9": 1, "Acme Corp": 1, "Northwind Research": 1, "13-02-2025": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00051", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 25 Nov 2015.\nGuest: We measured James Okafor on the study dated Marcus Chen.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Elena Volkov in Dr. Priya Sharma, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "25 Nov 2015", "label": "date", "start": 48, "end": 59}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 80, "end": 92}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 112, "end": 123}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 165, "end": 177}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 181, "end": 197}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 51, "document_seed": 321346522, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"25 Nov 2015": 1, "James Okafor": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00052", "text": "After reading about Hugging Face, I paired it with fine-tuning and tracked GPT-3 using Medium in Sam. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility.", "entities": [{"text": "Hugging Face", "label": "organization", "start": 20, "end": 32}, {"text": "fine-tuning", "label": "method", "start": 51, "end": 62}, {"text": "GPT-3", "label": "model", "start": 75, "end": 80}, {"text": "Medium", "label": "organization", "start": 87, "end": 93}, {"text": "Sam", "label": "person", "start": 97, "end": 100}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "blog_post", "document_type": "blog_post", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 52, "document_seed": 328553313, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Hugging Face": 1, "fine-tuning": 1, "GPT-3": 1, "Medium": 1, "Sam": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00053", "text": "Maria Garcia announced Jane Smith on 91.5, citing 66.8 from The Guardian. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Maria Garcia", "label": "person", "start": 0, "end": 12}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 23, "end": 33}, {"text": "91.5", "label": "number", "start": 37, "end": 41}, {"text": "66.8", "label": "number", "start": 50, "end": 54}, {"text": "The Guardian", "label": "organization", "start": 60, "end": 72}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 53, "document_seed": 1527429895, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Maria Garcia": 1, "Jane Smith": 1, "91.5": 1, "66.8": 1, "The Guardian": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00054", "text": "I tried attention mechanism with Alex last week and saw GPT-3 compared to Hugging Face on Jordan. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility.", "entities": [{"text": "attention mechanism", "label": "method", "start": 8, "end": 27}, {"text": "Alex", "label": "person", "start": 33, "end": 37}, {"text": "GPT-3", "label": "model", "start": 56, "end": 61}, {"text": "Hugging Face", "label": "organization", "start": 74, "end": 86}, {"text": "Jordan", "label": "person", "start": 90, "end": 96}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "blog_post", "document_type": "blog_post", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 54, "document_seed": 1317418898, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"attention mechanism": 1, "Alex": 1, "GPT-3": 1, "Hugging Face": 1, "Jordan": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00055", "text": "Officials in 26/10/2026 said 77.0 would affect Jane Smith after The Guardian reported Berlin. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "26/10/2026", "label": "date", "start": 13, "end": 23}, {"text": "77.0", "label": "number", "start": 29, "end": 33}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 47, "end": 57}, {"text": "The Guardian", "label": "organization", "start": 64, "end": 76}, {"text": "Berlin", "label": "location", "start": 86, "end": 92}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 55, "document_seed": 1149774302, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"26/10/2026": 1, "77.0": 1, "Jane Smith": 1, "The Guardian": 1, "Berlin": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00056", "text": "Officials in 04/03/2017 said New York would affect 14-09-2025 after 07/11/2017 reported BBC. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "04/03/2017", "label": "date", "start": 13, "end": 23}, {"text": "New York", "label": "location", "start": 29, "end": 37}, {"text": "14-09-2025", "label": "date", "start": 51, "end": 61}, {"text": "07/11/2017", "label": "date", "start": 68, "end": 78}, {"text": "BBC", "label": "organization", "start": 88, "end": 91}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 56, "document_seed": 1039110421, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"04/03/2017": 1, "New York": 1, "14-09-2025": 1, "07/11/2017": 1, "BBC": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00057", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Acme Corp.\nGuest: We measured James Okafor on the study dated 17,1.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is June 23, 2024 in Marcus Chen, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 48, "end": 57}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 78, "end": 90}, {"text": "17,1", "label": "number", "start": 110, "end": 114}, {"text": "June 23, 2024", "label": "date", "start": 156, "end": 169}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 173, "end": 184}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 57, "document_seed": 1565026304, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Acme Corp": 1, "James Okafor": 1, "17,1": 1, "June 23, 2024": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00058", "text": "Officials in John Doe said 38.2 would affect July 15, 2015 after Associated Press reported Maria Garcia. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 13, "end": 21}, {"text": "38.2", "label": "number", "start": 27, "end": 31}, {"text": "July 15, 2015", "label": "date", "start": 45, "end": 58}, {"text": "Associated Press", "label": "organization", "start": 65, "end": 81}, {"text": "Maria Garcia", "label": "person", "start": 91, "end": 103}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 58, "document_seed": 1778095122, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"John Doe": 1, "38.2": 1, "July 15, 2015": 1, "Associated Press": 1, "Maria Garcia": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00059", "text": "Tokyo announced BBC on 57,8, citing The Guardian from Reuters. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Tokyo", "label": "location", "start": 0, "end": 5}, {"text": "BBC", "label": "organization", "start": 16, "end": 19}, {"text": "57,8", "label": "number", "start": 23, "end": 27}, {"text": "The Guardian", "label": "organization", "start": 36, "end": 48}, {"text": "Reuters", "label": "organization", "start": 54, "end": 61}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 59, "document_seed": 1299655243, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Tokyo": 1, "BBC": 1, "57,8": 1, "The Guardian": 1, "Reuters": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00060", "text": "After reading about pre-training, I paired it with Sam and tracked Medium using Jordan in fine-tuning. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility.", "entities": [{"text": "pre-training", "label": "method", "start": 20, "end": 32}, {"text": "Sam", "label": "person", "start": 51, "end": 54}, {"text": "Medium", "label": "organization", "start": 67, "end": 73}, {"text": "Jordan", "label": "person", "start": 80, "end": 86}, {"text": "fine-tuning", "label": "method", "start": 90, "end": 101}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "blog_post", "document_type": "blog_post", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 60, "document_seed": 355803138, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"pre-training": 1, "Sam": 1, "Medium": 1, "Jordan": 1, "fine-tuning": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00061", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Pelorus Media.\nGuest: We measured Elena Volkov on the study dated 01 Aug 2026.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Acme Corp in Marcus Chen, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 48, "end": 61}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 82, "end": 94}, {"text": "01 Aug 2026", "label": "date", "start": 114, "end": 125}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 167, "end": 176}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 180, "end": 191}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 61, "document_seed": 481476888, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Pelorus Media": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1, "01 Aug 2026": 1, "Acme Corp": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00062", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at James Okafor.\nGuest: We measured Acme Corp on the study dated 20/07/2018.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Pelorus Media in 13,1, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 60}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 81, "end": 90}, {"text": "20/07/2018", "label": "date", "start": 110, "end": 120}, {"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 162, "end": 175}, {"text": "13,1", "label": "number", "start": 179, "end": 183}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 62, "document_seed": 466573753, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"James Okafor": 1, "Acme Corp": 1, "20/07/2018": 1, "Pelorus Media": 1, "13,1": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00063", "text": "After reading about fine-tuning, I paired it with BERT and tracked pre-training using attention mechanism in Sam. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility.", "entities": [{"text": "fine-tuning", "label": "method", "start": 20, "end": 31}, {"text": "BERT", "label": "model", "start": 50, "end": 54}, {"text": "pre-training", "label": "method", "start": 67, "end": 79}, {"text": "attention mechanism", "label": "method", "start": 86, "end": 105}, {"text": "Sam", "label": "person", "start": 109, "end": 112}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "blog_post", "document_type": "blog_post", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 63, "document_seed": 2113683471, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"fine-tuning": 1, "BERT": 1, "pre-training": 1, "attention mechanism": 1, "Sam": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00064", "text": "After reading about attention mechanism, I paired it with Jordan and tracked BERT using Hugging Face in fine-tuning. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility.", "entities": [{"text": "attention mechanism", "label": "method", "start": 20, "end": 39}, {"text": "Jordan", "label": "person", "start": 58, "end": 64}, {"text": "BERT", "label": "model", "start": 77, "end": 81}, {"text": "Hugging Face", "label": "organization", "start": 88, "end": 100}, {"text": "fine-tuning", "label": "method", "start": 104, "end": 115}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "blog_post", "document_type": "blog_post", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 64, "document_seed": 718050962, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"attention mechanism": 1, "Jordan": 1, "BERT": 1, "Hugging Face": 1, "fine-tuning": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00065", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Marcus Chen.\nGuest: We measured 6.2 on the study dated Northwind Research.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Elena Volkov in James Okafor, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 59}, {"text": "6.2", "label": "number", "start": 80, "end": 83}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 103, "end": 121}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 163, "end": 175}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 179, "end": 191}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 65, "document_seed": 1874706727, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Marcus Chen": 1, "6.2": 1, "Northwind Research": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1, "James Okafor": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00066", "text": "Officials in The Guardian said 01/04/2023 would affect 7.7 after 02 Feb 2020 reported John Doe. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "The Guardian", "label": "organization", "start": 13, "end": 25}, {"text": "01/04/2023", "label": "date", "start": 31, "end": 41}, {"text": "7.7", "label": "number", "start": 55, "end": 58}, {"text": "02 Feb 2020", "label": "date", "start": 65, "end": 76}, {"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 86, "end": 94}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 66, "document_seed": 1460015728, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"The Guardian": 1, "01/04/2023": 1, "7.7": 1, "02 Feb 2020": 1, "John Doe": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00067", "text": "Jane Smith announced John Doe on 14,1, citing 28-05-2021 from New York. Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 0, "end": 10}, {"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 21, "end": 29}, {"text": "14,1", "label": "number", "start": 33, "end": 37}, {"text": "28-05-2021", "label": "date", "start": 46, "end": 56}, {"text": "New York", "label": "location", "start": 62, "end": 70}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 67, "document_seed": 374029944, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Jane Smith": 1, "John Doe": 1, "14,1": 1, "28-05-2021": 1, "New York": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000105-00068", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at James Okafor.\nGuest: We measured 29 Oct 2017 on the study dated Pelorus Media.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is 18 Nov 2015 in Elena Volkov, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 60}, {"text": "29 Oct 2017", "label": "date", "start": 81, "end": 92}, {"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 112, "end": 125}, {"text": "18 Nov 2015", "label": "date", "start": 167, "end": 178}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 182, "end": 194}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 105, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 68, "document_seed": 1055221398, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"James Okafor": 1, "29 Oct 2017": 1, "Pelorus Media": 1, "18 Nov 2015": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1}}}}
