{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00000", "text": "Associated Press reported on Tuesday that a new data‑privacy law will take effect across the European Union next month, prompting telecom firms to overhaul their consent protocols. The Guardian cited industry analysts who warned of compliance costs reaching billions of euros, while Reuters confirmed that regulators will impose steep fines for violations. In response, Jane Smith, a senior legal advisor at a leading firm, said the measures are \"necessary to protect citizens' digital rights\". The BBC will continue to monitor the rollout and its impact on consumers.", "entities": [{"text": "Associated Press", "label": "organization", "start": 0, "end": 16}, {"text": "The Guardian", "label": "organization", "start": 181, "end": 193}, {"text": "Reuters", "label": "organization", "start": 283, "end": 290}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 370, "end": 380}, {"text": "BBC", "label": "organization", "start": 499, "end": 502}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 0, "document_seed": 836464178, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Associated Press": 1, "The Guardian": 1, "Reuters": 1, "Jane Smith": 1, "BBC": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00001", "text": "May 30, 2016 — A multi‑national consortium of media outlets announced today that they will jointly fund a new investigative journalism hub focused on climate resilience. The effort, coordinated by The Guardian and supported by Associated Press, will pool resources to train reporters in data‑driven storytelling. Reuters will provide technical assistance and a secure platform for data exchange. Jane Smith, the appointed director of the initiative, said the partnership aims to amplify under‑reported stories and ensure broader public access to critical environmental information.", "entities": [{"text": "May 30, 2016", "label": "date", "start": 0, "end": 12}, {"text": "The Guardian", "label": "organization", "start": 197, "end": 209}, {"text": "Associated Press", "label": "organization", "start": 227, "end": 243}, {"text": "Reuters", "label": "organization", "start": 313, "end": 320}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 396, "end": 406}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 1, "document_seed": 1540496234, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"The Guardian": 1, "Associated Press": 1, "Jane Smith": 1, "Reuters": 1, "May 30, 2016": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00002", "text": "A new health study released on Tuesday indicates that the average daily screen time among adolescents has risen to 42.6 minutes, prompting officials to call for tighter guidelines. Researchers from a leading university highlighted the surge in digital consumption and its potential impact on sleep patterns and academic performance. The report was first cited by Maria Garcia, a spokesperson for the national health agency, during a briefing that was broadcast by BBC. In response, John Doe, editor-in-chief of The Guardian, said the findings underscore the need for coordinated public‑health messaging to address emerging lifestyle risks.", "entities": [{"text": "42.6", "label": "number", "start": 115, "end": 119}, {"text": "Maria Garcia", "label": "person", "start": 363, "end": 375}, {"text": "BBC", "label": "organization", "start": 464, "end": 467}, {"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 482, "end": 490}, {"text": "The Guardian", "label": "organization", "start": 511, "end": 523}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 2, "document_seed": 2006345357, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"42.6": 1, "Maria Garcia": 1, "BBC": 1, "John Doe": 1, "The Guardian": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00003", "text": "Berlin – A municipal report released today confirms that the city’s housing initiative, first launched on 30-04-2017, has met its initial occupancy targets. The program, which was modeled after a pilot study conducted on November 25, 2015, aims to provide affordable units to low‑income families. Officials noted that the latest construction phase, scheduled to begin on 04/09/2021, will add 1,200 new apartments. A mid‑term review set for 14-10-2018 will assess long‑term sustainability and budget compliance.", "entities": [{"text": "Berlin", "label": "location", "start": 0, "end": 6}, {"text": "30-04-2017", "label": "date", "start": 106, "end": 116}, {"text": "November 25, 2015", "label": "date", "start": 221, "end": 238}, {"text": "04/09/2021", "label": "date", "start": 371, "end": 381}, {"text": "14-10-2018", "label": "date", "start": 440, "end": 450}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 3, "document_seed": 208396045, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"30-04-2017": 1, "Berlin": 1, "November 25, 2015": 1, "04/09/2021": 1, "14-10-2018": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00004", "text": "New York — The Associated Press reported on Thursday that the city’s public schools will begin a pilot nutrition program next month, aimed at improving student health outcomes. The initiative, unveiled by education officials on 17-02-2017, will initially serve 30 schools and feature fresh fruit, vegetables, and whole‑grain options in cafeteria meals. Maria Garcia, the district’s nutrition director, said the menu changes are based on recent dietary studies and community feedback. Jane Smith, a parent of two elementary students, welcomed the effort, noting that healthier meals could boost both concentration and overall well‑being among children.", "entities": [{"text": "New York", "label": "location", "start": 0, "end": 8}, {"text": "Associated Press", "label": "organization", "start": 15, "end": 31}, {"text": "17-02-2017", "label": "date", "start": 228, "end": 238}, {"text": "Maria Garcia", "label": "person", "start": 353, "end": 365}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 484, "end": 494}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 4, "document_seed": 921369128, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"New York": 1, "Associated Press": 1, "Maria Garcia": 1, "Jane Smith": 1, "17-02-2017": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00005", "text": "John Doe arrived in Tokyo on 04/02/2015 to attend a diplomatic forum hosted by the BBC. The attendee, a senior economic analyst, delivered a briefing on emerging market trends before traveling to Berlin for a follow‑up meeting with European policymakers. Officials said the discussions in both cities aim to strengthen trade ties and address supply‑chain challenges, with results to be reported in a joint statement later this month.", "entities": [{"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 0, "end": 8}, {"text": "Tokyo", "label": "location", "start": 20, "end": 25}, {"text": "04/02/2015", "label": "date", "start": 29, "end": 39}, {"text": "BBC", "label": "organization", "start": 83, "end": 86}, {"text": "Berlin", "label": "location", "start": 196, "end": 202}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 5, "document_seed": 952178134, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"John Doe": 1, "04/02/2015": 1, "BBC": 1, "Tokyo": 1, "Berlin": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00006", "text": "The European Central Bank announced on 17-09-2025 that its inflation outlook has been adjusted following the latest consumer price data. The central bank noted that the annual inflation rate fell to 73.9 percent in the fourth quarter, a sharp decline from earlier estimates. The report also referenced the previous forecast released on December 17, 2022 and the interim assessment dated 10-03-2023, highlighting the evolution of policy assumptions over the past three years. Economists expect the upcoming policy meeting scheduled for 12-10-2026 to focus on whether the downward trend will continue, with the ECB signifying a cautious approach to interest‑rate changes while maintaining its commitment to price stability.", "entities": [{"text": "17-09-2025", "label": "date", "start": 39, "end": 49}, {"text": "73.9", "label": "number", "start": 199, "end": 203}, {"text": "December 17, 2022", "label": "date", "start": 336, "end": 353}, {"text": "10-03-2023", "label": "date", "start": 387, "end": 397}, {"text": "12-10-2026", "label": "date", "start": 535, "end": 545}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 6, "document_seed": 1239194420, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"17-09-2025": 1, "December 17, 2022": 1, "10-03-2023": 1, "73.9": 1, "12-10-2026": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00007", "text": "14-12-2023 – A multinational trade conference took place in New York, drawing attention from global markets. Reuters reported that the summit focused on post‑pandemic supply chain resilience, with officials from several countries exchanging data and policy proposals.\n\nDuring a plenary session, John Doe, senior analyst at a leading consultancy, presented a briefing on emerging logistics trends, citing recent developments in London as a case study for urban freight optimization. The event concluded with a joint statement urging coordinated investment to safeguard future trade flows.", "entities": [{"text": "14-12-2023", "label": "date", "start": 0, "end": 10}, {"text": "New York", "label": "location", "start": 60, "end": 68}, {"text": "Reuters", "label": "organization", "start": 109, "end": 116}, {"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 295, "end": 303}, {"text": "London", "label": "location", "start": 427, "end": 433}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 7, "document_seed": 2085050136, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"14-12-2023": 1, "New York": 1, "Reuters": 1, "London": 1, "John Doe": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00008", "text": "London, 22-08-2022 – A new economic report released today shows that consumer confidence in the eurozone has risen to a read of 20.2, the highest level in two years. The Associated Press cited data from the European Central Bank, noting that the improvement is driven by stronger retail sales and a modest rebound in manufacturing output. Analysts in Berlin warned that the gains could be fragile, but the overall trend suggests a gradual stabilization of the region’s economy.", "entities": [{"text": "London", "label": "location", "start": 0, "end": 6}, {"text": "22-08-2022", "label": "date", "start": 8, "end": 18}, {"text": "20.2", "label": "number", "start": 128, "end": 132}, {"text": "Associated Press", "label": "organization", "start": 170, "end": 186}, {"text": "Berlin", "label": "location", "start": 351, "end": 357}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 8, "document_seed": 912151271, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"20.2": 1, "Associated Press": 1, "London": 1, "Berlin": 1, "22-08-2022": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00009", "text": "25/02/2020 – New York – A city council meeting on Tuesday resulted in the approval of a new affordable‑housing ordinance, marking the first major legislative win for local activists this year. The measure, which mandates a 20% increase in low‑income units in all new developments, was championed by councilmember John Doe, who said the policy will address the city’s growing housing shortage. Reporting on the vote, The Guardian noted the bipartisan support, while Reuters highlighted the potential ripple effect on neighboring municipalities.", "entities": [{"text": "25/02/2020", "label": "date", "start": 0, "end": 10}, {"text": "New York", "label": "location", "start": 13, "end": 21}, {"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 313, "end": 321}, {"text": "The Guardian", "label": "organization", "start": 416, "end": 428}, {"text": "Reuters", "label": "organization", "start": 465, "end": 472}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 9, "document_seed": 1413205252, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"25/02/2020": 1, "New York": 1, "John Doe": 1, "The Guardian": 1, "Reuters": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00010", "text": "Berlin – A joint statement issued on 05/08/2022 announced the launch of a renewable‑energy consortium aimed at cutting regional carbon emissions by 30% within five years. The initiative, overseen by project director Jane Smith, received additional funding on 07 Mar 2024 after a review confirmed the pilot’s early success in reducing grid reliance on fossil fuels. Officials said the program will expand to include new infrastructure projects, with the next phase slated to begin on November 22, 2025, marking a critical milestone for the city’s climate goals.", "entities": [{"text": "Berlin", "label": "location", "start": 0, "end": 6}, {"text": "05/08/2022", "label": "date", "start": 37, "end": 47}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 216, "end": 226}, {"text": "07 Mar 2024", "label": "date", "start": 259, "end": 270}, {"text": "November 22, 2025", "label": "date", "start": 483, "end": 500}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 10, "document_seed": 1881118470, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"05/08/2022": 1, "07 Mar 2024": 1, "November 22, 2025": 1, "Berlin": 1, "Jane Smith": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00011", "text": "London – A joint economic survey released on 26-11-2019 showed that the median household savings rate rose to 63.1 percent, outpacing the previous quarter's modest gain. The report, compiled by a team led by analyst John Doe, attributes the increase to a combination of lower consumer debt and higher disposable income across major urban centers. Policymakers in Berlin are monitoring the data closely, citing the figure as a potential indicator for upcoming fiscal adjustments.", "entities": [{"text": "London", "label": "location", "start": 0, "end": 6}, {"text": "26-11-2019", "label": "date", "start": 45, "end": 55}, {"text": "63.1", "label": "number", "start": 110, "end": 114}, {"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 216, "end": 224}, {"text": "Berlin", "label": "location", "start": 363, "end": 369}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 11, "document_seed": 302174501, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"63.1": 1, "London": 1, "John Doe": 1, "Berlin": 1, "26-11-2019": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00012", "text": "London – A joint statement released today by the BBC and Reuters confirmed that the newly launched public transport fare system achieved an average ridership increase of 75.3 percent during its first month. The report quoted project coordinator Maria Garcia, who said the numbers demonstrate strong community response and will guide future pricing adjustments. Authorities plan to monitor trends closely and issue further updates next quarter.", "entities": [{"text": "London", "label": "location", "start": 0, "end": 6}, {"text": "BBC", "label": "organization", "start": 49, "end": 52}, {"text": "Reuters", "label": "organization", "start": 57, "end": 64}, {"text": "75.3", "label": "number", "start": 170, "end": 174}, {"text": "Maria Garcia", "label": "person", "start": 245, "end": 257}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 12, "document_seed": 1096255766, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"London": 1, "BBC": 1, "Reuters": 1, "Maria Garcia": 1, "75.3": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00013", "text": "Berlin – A multinational tech conference opened today with a keynote address from John Doe, who highlighted the rapid growth of artificial‑intelligence startups across major hubs. He noted that investors are increasingly focusing on ecosystems in New York, Tokyo and London, citing recent funding rounds that demonstrate a shift toward global collaboration. Organizers said the event will feature panel discussions on cross‑border regulation and future talent pipelines, aiming to foster partnerships that span these four key cities.", "entities": [{"text": "Berlin", "label": "location", "start": 0, "end": 6}, {"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 82, "end": 90}, {"text": "New York", "label": "location", "start": 247, "end": 255}, {"text": "Tokyo", "label": "location", "start": 257, "end": 262}, {"text": "London", "label": "location", "start": 267, "end": 273}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 13, "document_seed": 830159750, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Berlin": 1, "John Doe": 1, "New York": 1, "Tokyo": 1, "London": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00014", "text": "Berlin – A new cultural partnership was announced today, linking local museums with international media outlets. Maria Garcia, the city's director of arts initiatives, said the agreement will feature joint exhibitions and multimedia projects. The BBC and The Guardian will each contribute editorial content and coverage, while John Doe, appointed as liaison officer, will oversee the coordination between the partners.", "entities": [{"text": "Berlin", "label": "location", "start": 0, "end": 6}, {"text": "Maria Garcia", "label": "person", "start": 113, "end": 125}, {"text": "BBC", "label": "organization", "start": 247, "end": 250}, {"text": "The Guardian", "label": "organization", "start": 255, "end": 267}, {"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 327, "end": 335}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 14, "document_seed": 691775673, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Berlin": 1, "Maria Garcia": 1, "BBC": 1, "The Guardian": 1, "John Doe": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00015", "text": "John Doe announced on 28-03-2020 that his company would launch a new sustainability initiative aimed at reducing urban waste. The statement was released simultaneously to BBC and Reuters, confirming the project's focus on partnering with local authorities. The pilot program will begin next month in New York, where officials expect measurable environmental benefits within the first year.", "entities": [{"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 0, "end": 8}, {"text": "28-03-2020", "label": "date", "start": 22, "end": 32}, {"text": "BBC", "label": "organization", "start": 171, "end": 174}, {"text": "Reuters", "label": "organization", "start": 179, "end": 186}, {"text": "New York", "label": "location", "start": 300, "end": 308}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 15, "document_seed": 381666133, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"John Doe": 1, "28-03-2020": 1, "BBC": 1, "Reuters": 1, "New York": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00016", "text": "John Doe and Maria Garcia were announced as the new co‑editors of The Guardian on 29-03-2022, succeeding a long‑standing editorial team amid a reshuffle aimed at expanding digital coverage. The partnership, which was first reported on 08 Dec 2017, is expected to bring a blend of investigative rigor and multimedia storytelling to the newspaper’s global audience. Management said the appointment reflects a commitment to diverse perspectives and reinforces the outlet’s reputation for independent journalism.", "entities": [{"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 0, "end": 8}, {"text": "Maria Garcia", "label": "person", "start": 13, "end": 25}, {"text": "The Guardian", "label": "organization", "start": 66, "end": 78}, {"text": "29-03-2022", "label": "date", "start": 82, "end": 92}, {"text": "08 Dec 2017", "label": "date", "start": 235, "end": 246}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 16, "document_seed": 1912169913, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"John Doe": 1, "Maria Garcia": 1, "The Guardian": 1, "29-03-2022": 1, "08 Dec 2017": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00017", "text": "Tokyo – A multinational consortium announced today that it will launch a joint research initiative aimed at advancing renewable energy storage technologies. The project, which will be coordinated from a headquarters in Berlin, brings together leading laboratories from Europe and Asia to develop next‑generation battery systems. In a statement, project director Jane Smith said the collaboration will accelerate commercialization timelines and create new jobs across the partner regions.\n\nThe effort also includes a strategic partnership with a technology hub in New York, allowing the consortium to tap into the city's extensive venture capital network. Additionally, a research exchange program will be established with universities in London, fostering knowledge sharing and joint publications over the next five years.", "entities": [{"text": "Tokyo", "label": "location", "start": 0, "end": 5}, {"text": "Berlin", "label": "location", "start": 219, "end": 225}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 362, "end": 372}, {"text": "New York", "label": "location", "start": 563, "end": 571}, {"text": "London", "label": "location", "start": 738, "end": 744}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 17, "document_seed": 1574169845, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Tokyo": 1, "New York": 1, "London": 1, "Berlin": 1, "Jane Smith": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00018", "text": "A protest rally in downtown Madrid drew an unexpected turnout of 69,0 participants, according to police estimates. Organizers, led by activist John Doe, called for tighter regulations on digital privacy after recent data breaches. The Guardian reported that authorities arrested several demonstrators for violating public assembly rules, while the BBC confirmed that no injuries were reported. Maria Garcia, a local lawyer, said the crowd's concerns reflect growing public anxiety over online security.", "entities": [{"text": "69,0", "label": "number", "start": 65, "end": 69}, {"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 143, "end": 151}, {"text": "The Guardian", "label": "organization", "start": 231, "end": 243}, {"text": "BBC", "label": "organization", "start": 348, "end": 351}, {"text": "Maria Garcia", "label": "person", "start": 394, "end": 406}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 18, "document_seed": 822964419, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"69,0": 1, "John Doe": 1, "The Guardian": 1, "BBC": 1, "Maria Garcia": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00019", "text": "01 Jul 2023 — A federal health agency released its quarterly performance report, noting a rise in vaccination coverage to 95.4 percent among adults. The data, compiled from clinics across the United States, underscore progress since the pandemic’s peak. Analysts highlighted that the trend began after a series of outreach programs launched on 29-04-2021, which targeted underserved communities.\n\nThe agency plans to hold a press briefing in New York next month to discuss upcoming initiatives and to outline goals for the upcoming fiscal year, with a key milestone set for September 27, 2024, when a new digital health platform will go live.", "entities": [{"text": "01 Jul 2023", "label": "date", "start": 0, "end": 11}, {"text": "95.4", "label": "number", "start": 122, "end": 126}, {"text": "29-04-2021", "label": "date", "start": 344, "end": 354}, {"text": "New York", "label": "location", "start": 442, "end": 450}, {"text": "September 27, 2024", "label": "date", "start": 574, "end": 592}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 19, "document_seed": 2025859891, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"01 Jul 2023": 1, "95.4": 1, "29-04-2021": 1, "New York": 1, "September 27, 2024": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00020", "text": "BBC reports that a public health conference held in London drew attention from both local officials and international experts. Maria Garcia, the event coordinator, highlighted the importance of cross‑border collaboration, while research presented by John Doe emphasized new vaccine distribution strategies. In a closing statement, Jane Smith, a senior policy adviser, called for sustained funding to ensure the initiatives discussed can be implemented promptly.", "entities": [{"text": "BBC", "label": "organization", "start": 0, "end": 3}, {"text": "London", "label": "location", "start": 52, "end": 58}, {"text": "Maria Garcia", "label": "person", "start": 127, "end": 139}, {"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 250, "end": 258}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 331, "end": 341}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 20, "document_seed": 1400280754, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"BBC": 1, "Maria Garcia": 1, "John Doe": 1, "London": 1, "Jane Smith": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00021", "text": "Tokyo – On 18-10-2020 the national statistics office released its latest consumer confidence figures, showing a modest rise to 76.2 points. The upward movement was attributed to easing retail restrictions and a slight improvement in employment trends.\n\nThe report, cited by the BBC, also highlighted that the manufacturing index slipped to 82,6, indicating lingering challenges in the production sector. Officials said the mixed signals will guide policy adjustments in the coming months as the economy seeks stable growth.", "entities": [{"text": "Tokyo", "label": "location", "start": 0, "end": 5}, {"text": "18-10-2020", "label": "date", "start": 11, "end": 21}, {"text": "76.2", "label": "number", "start": 127, "end": 131}, {"text": "BBC", "label": "organization", "start": 278, "end": 281}, {"text": "82,6", "label": "number", "start": 340, "end": 344}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 21, "document_seed": 1025725474, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"76.2": 1, "Tokyo": 1, "18-10-2020": 1, "82,6": 1, "BBC": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00022", "text": "January 11, 2018 – A joint report released today highlighted a surge in consumer confidence, with the index climbing to 84.0 points, the highest reading in over a year. The analysis, compiled by Reuters and corroborated by independent data, cited stronger employment figures and a rebound in retail sales as key drivers of the optimism. The report also noted that New York saw a particularly robust recovery, with local businesses reporting increased foot traffic and higher average transaction values.\n\nIn related coverage, the Associated Press noted that policymakers are monitoring the trend closely, warning that any reversal could affect upcoming fiscal decisions. Analysts predict that if the upward momentum continues, the market could see further gains in the fourth quarter, reinforcing the positive outlook established earlier this month.", "entities": [{"text": "January 11, 2018", "label": "date", "start": 0, "end": 16}, {"text": "84.0", "label": "number", "start": 120, "end": 124}, {"text": "Reuters", "label": "organization", "start": 195, "end": 202}, {"text": "New York", "label": "location", "start": 364, "end": 372}, {"text": "Associated Press", "label": "organization", "start": 529, "end": 545}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 22, "document_seed": 1734712929, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"January 11, 2018": 1, "84.0": 1, "Reuters": 1, "New York": 1, "Associated Press": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00023", "text": "BBC reported on Tuesday that Maria Garcia, the newly appointed director of cultural exchange, arrived in Tokyo for a series of bilateral meetings. The agenda includes discussions on arts funding and joint exhibitions, with a scheduled press conference featuring Jane Smith, the senior correspondent covering the event. Officials in New York said the initiative aims to strengthen ties between the two cities and expand collaborative programs.", "entities": [{"text": "BBC", "label": "organization", "start": 0, "end": 3}, {"text": "Maria Garcia", "label": "person", "start": 29, "end": 41}, {"text": "Tokyo", "label": "location", "start": 105, "end": 110}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 262, "end": 272}, {"text": "New York", "label": "location", "start": 332, "end": 340}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 23, "document_seed": 1813773526, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"BBC": 1, "Maria Garcia": 1, "Tokyo": 1, "Jane Smith": 1, "New York": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00024", "text": "07-03-2019 – The Guardian reported today that a landmark environmental settlement will be finalized later this year, marking a significant step for the region's renewable energy targets. The agreement, negotiated over two years, was signed by the lead attorney Jane Smith, who hailed the deal as a model for future public‑private collaborations.\n\nThe settlement builds on a prior framework established on 16-05-2018, when the initial memorandum of understanding was signed by policy adviser John Doe. Officials expect the new terms to accelerate investments and create thousands of jobs, while providing measurable reductions in carbon emissions.", "entities": [{"text": "07-03-2019", "label": "date", "start": 0, "end": 10}, {"text": "The Guardian", "label": "organization", "start": 13, "end": 25}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 261, "end": 271}, {"text": "16-05-2018", "label": "date", "start": 405, "end": 415}, {"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 491, "end": 499}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 24, "document_seed": 894502986, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"07-03-2019": 1, "The Guardian": 1, "Jane Smith": 1, "16-05-2018": 1, "John Doe": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00025", "text": "Berlin – A joint news briefing held Tuesday highlighted new trade guidelines for the European market. Representatives from three major wire services addressed questions, with the spokesperson for the Associated Press noting the cooperative effort, while a senior editor at Reuters emphasized data transparency. The BBC’s foreign correspondent added context about regional impact. The briefing was led by Jane Smith, senior policy analyst, who outlined the next steps for implementation and invited stakeholders to submit feedback by the end of the month.", "entities": [{"text": "Berlin", "label": "location", "start": 0, "end": 6}, {"text": "Associated Press", "label": "organization", "start": 200, "end": 216}, {"text": "Reuters", "label": "organization", "start": 273, "end": 280}, {"text": "BBC", "label": "organization", "start": 315, "end": 318}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 404, "end": 414}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 25, "document_seed": 270148938, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Associated Press": 1, "Reuters": 1, "BBC": 1, "Jane Smith": 1, "Berlin": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00026", "text": "Associated Press reported on Tuesday that a new public health study released in New York shows a 48.6 percent increase in vaccination rates among seniors. The research, conducted by a coalition of local hospitals, was presented at a press conference attended by city officials and health experts. Maria Garcia, the study’s lead epidemiologist, said the data points to successful outreach programs and hopes the trend will continue. The findings were also highlighted in a BBC briefing later in the day, emphasizing the community’s role in combating preventable diseases.", "entities": [{"text": "Associated Press", "label": "organization", "start": 0, "end": 16}, {"text": "New York", "label": "location", "start": 80, "end": 88}, {"text": "48.6", "label": "number", "start": 97, "end": 101}, {"text": "Maria Garcia", "label": "person", "start": 297, "end": 309}, {"text": "BBC", "label": "organization", "start": 472, "end": 475}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 26, "document_seed": 1847497524, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Associated Press": 1, "Maria Garcia": 1, "BBC": 1, "48.6": 1, "New York": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00027", "text": "Reuters reported on Wednesday that officials in Tokyo and Berlin have agreed to a joint initiative aimed at streamlining cross‑border data transfers. The cooperation will be overseen by a newly formed committee that will meet first in New York later this month to outline regulatory frameworks. The Associated Press confirmed that the agreement is expected to enhance digital trade while maintaining privacy standards across the participating regions.", "entities": [{"text": "Reuters", "label": "organization", "start": 0, "end": 7}, {"text": "Tokyo", "label": "location", "start": 48, "end": 53}, {"text": "Berlin", "label": "location", "start": 58, "end": 64}, {"text": "New York", "label": "location", "start": 235, "end": 243}, {"text": "Associated Press", "label": "organization", "start": 299, "end": 315}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 27, "document_seed": 2008824142, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Tokyo": 1, "Berlin": 1, "Reuters": 1, "New York": 1, "Associated Press": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00028", "text": "Associated Press – A city council voted Tuesday to approve a new public‑transport funding plan that will allocate 99,7 million dollars over the next five years, aiming to reduce traffic congestion and lower emissions. The measure was championed by councilmember John Doe, who highlighted the project's potential to create jobs and improve commuter safety. Opposition leader Jane Smith argued the budget could strain municipal finances, calling for a phased rollout. Reuters reported that the council expects the program to launch in early 2027, pending final regulatory approvals.", "entities": [{"text": "Associated Press", "label": "organization", "start": 0, "end": 16}, {"text": "99,7", "label": "number", "start": 114, "end": 118}, {"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 262, "end": 270}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 374, "end": 384}, {"text": "Reuters", "label": "organization", "start": 466, "end": 473}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 28, "document_seed": 1306914810, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"John Doe": 1, "Jane Smith": 1, "99,7": 1, "Associated Press": 1, "Reuters": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00029", "text": "Tokyo – On 03 Sep 2016, officials confirmed that a new high‑speed rail line will link the capital with regional hubs, aiming to cut travel times by up to 30 percent. The project, funded jointly by the national government and private investors, is expected to begin construction later this year and create thousands of jobs. The Guardian reported that the initiative reflects Japan’s broader push for infrastructure modernization, while the BBC noted similar upgrades are planned for other Asian cities. London officials praised the collaboration as a model for international transport development.", "entities": [{"text": "Tokyo", "label": "location", "start": 0, "end": 5}, {"text": "03 Sep 2016", "label": "date", "start": 11, "end": 22}, {"text": "The Guardian", "label": "organization", "start": 324, "end": 336}, {"text": "BBC", "label": "organization", "start": 440, "end": 443}, {"text": "London", "label": "location", "start": 503, "end": 509}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 29, "document_seed": 909449670, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Tokyo": 1, "The Guardian": 1, "03 Sep 2016": 1, "BBC": 1, "London": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00030", "text": "The quarterly report was prepared by John Doe, who coordinated the data collection across two major hubs. In London, the finance team verified the expense tables, while in New York the marketing analysts compiled customer feedback. Maria Garcia oversaw the technical validation, ensuring that every spreadsheet matched the prescribed format. After a series of internal reviews, Jane Smith signed off on the final version, confirming that all metrics were accurate and the narrative was clear. The document was then distributed to senior leadership for approval, marking the completion of the project before the deadline.", "entities": [{"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 37, "end": 45}, {"text": "London", "label": "location", "start": 109, "end": 115}, {"text": "New York", "label": "location", "start": 172, "end": 180}, {"text": "Maria Garcia", "label": "person", "start": 232, "end": 244}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 378, "end": 388}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 30, "document_seed": 475878699, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Maria Garcia": 1, "London": 1, "New York": 1, "Jane Smith": 1, "John Doe": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00031", "text": "Tokyo, 26 Dec 2020 – A multinational conference on renewable energy concluded today with officials reporting that 48 new projects were approved for funding. The announcements were made during a joint press briefing in Berlin, where Maria Garcia, director of the Global Climate Initiative, highlighted the significance of cross‑border collaboration. Participants said the initiatives will accelerate the transition to low‑carbon technologies across Europe and Asia.", "entities": [{"text": "Tokyo", "label": "location", "start": 0, "end": 5}, {"text": "26 Dec 2020", "label": "date", "start": 7, "end": 18}, {"text": "48", "label": "number", "start": 114, "end": 116}, {"text": "Berlin", "label": "location", "start": 218, "end": 224}, {"text": "Maria Garcia", "label": "person", "start": 232, "end": 244}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 31, "document_seed": 1411032157, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"48": 1, "Maria Garcia": 1, "26 Dec 2020": 1, "Tokyo": 1, "Berlin": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00032", "text": "BBC reports that an international summit on renewable energy was convened in Tokyo on 31-01-2016, drawing officials from across the sector. The meeting, co‑hosted by the city government and industry leaders, featured a keynote address by Maria Garcia, who highlighted recent advances in solar storage technology. Reuters noted that the agenda included commitments to reduce carbon emissions by 2030, and officials indicated that the agreements reached could set new standards for global collaboration on climate initiatives.", "entities": [{"text": "BBC", "label": "organization", "start": 0, "end": 3}, {"text": "Tokyo", "label": "location", "start": 77, "end": 82}, {"text": "31-01-2016", "label": "date", "start": 86, "end": 96}, {"text": "Maria Garcia", "label": "person", "start": 238, "end": 250}, {"text": "Reuters", "label": "organization", "start": 313, "end": 320}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 32, "document_seed": 1148124468, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"BBC": 1, "Maria Garcia": 1, "Tokyo": 1, "Reuters": 1, "31-01-2016": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00033", "text": "London—The Associated Press reported Tuesday that Jane Smith, a senior analyst, presented the latest economic forecast indicating a growth rate of 79,1 percent for the upcoming quarter. The briefing, held in New York, highlighted the potential impact of new fiscal policies on both domestic and international markets. Officials said the projection reflects current trends and will be monitored closely as data continues to emerge.", "entities": [{"text": "London", "label": "location", "start": 0, "end": 6}, {"text": "Associated Press", "label": "organization", "start": 11, "end": 27}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 50, "end": 60}, {"text": "79,1", "label": "number", "start": 147, "end": 151}, {"text": "New York", "label": "location", "start": 208, "end": 216}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 33, "document_seed": 1694978474, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Jane Smith": 1, "London": 1, "Associated Press": 1, "79,1": 1, "New York": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00034", "text": "Sept. 15 — A coordinated statement released on September 15, 2021 confirmed that three major news outlets will jointly investigate the offshore financial disclosures that have sparked global debate. Reuters, Associated Press and BBC each announced plans to collaborate with independent auditors and legal experts to verify the authenticity of the leaked documents, emphasizing a commitment to transparency and public interest. The Guardian noted that the partnership reflects an unprecedented level of cross‑media cooperation, aiming to deliver exhaustive reporting while safeguarding source confidentiality.", "entities": [{"text": "September 15, 2021", "label": "date", "start": 47, "end": 65}, {"text": "Reuters", "label": "organization", "start": 199, "end": 206}, {"text": "Associated Press", "label": "organization", "start": 208, "end": 224}, {"text": "BBC", "label": "organization", "start": 229, "end": 232}, {"text": "The Guardian", "label": "organization", "start": 427, "end": 439}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 34, "document_seed": 1628988057, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Reuters": 1, "Associated Press": 1, "BBC": 1, "September 15, 2021": 1, "The Guardian": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00035", "text": "Reuters reported on 20-08-2023 that officials in Berlin and London are poised to sign a bilateral trade accord aimed at easing tariffs on key commodities. The announcement came after weeks of negotiation facilitated by the Associated Press, which highlighted the potential economic benefits for both economies. The forthcoming agreement is expected to boost cross‑border investment and strengthen supply‑chain resilience, analysts say.", "entities": [{"text": "Reuters", "label": "organization", "start": 0, "end": 7}, {"text": "20-08-2023", "label": "date", "start": 20, "end": 30}, {"text": "Berlin", "label": "location", "start": 49, "end": 55}, {"text": "London", "label": "location", "start": 60, "end": 66}, {"text": "Associated Press", "label": "organization", "start": 223, "end": 239}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 35, "document_seed": 984052114, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Reuters": 1, "20-08-2023": 1, "Associated Press": 1, "Berlin": 1, "London": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00036", "text": "Tokyo – On 18 Dec 2024, officials released a quarterly growth report that showed the national economy expanding at an annualized rate of 59.3 percent, surpassing analysts’ expectations. The data, compiled by the finance ministry, highlighted a rebound in consumer spending and a modest rise in manufacturing output. Both the Associated Press and Reuters were cited as primary sources for the figures, which officials said reflect the impact of recent fiscal stimulus measures and a stabilising currency.", "entities": [{"text": "Tokyo", "label": "location", "start": 0, "end": 5}, {"text": "18 Dec 2024", "label": "date", "start": 11, "end": 22}, {"text": "59.3", "label": "number", "start": 137, "end": 141}, {"text": "Associated Press", "label": "organization", "start": 325, "end": 341}, {"text": "Reuters", "label": "organization", "start": 346, "end": 353}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 36, "document_seed": 1816629581, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Tokyo": 1, "18 Dec 2024": 1, "Associated Press": 1, "Reuters": 1, "59.3": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00037", "text": "London – A court in the capital issued a ruling on corporate liability on January 12, 2015 that will affect dozens of small enterprises. The decision, cited by the Associated Press, stems from a complaint filed by consumer advocate Maria Garcia, who argued that the existing regulations were insufficient to protect shoppers.\nThe judgment was upheld after a hearing on 15/02/2017, when the judges confirmed the earlier findings and ordered the defendant to amend its policies within 90 days. Officials said the case sets a precedent for future enforcement actions across the United Kingdom.", "entities": [{"text": "London", "label": "location", "start": 0, "end": 6}, {"text": "January 12, 2015", "label": "date", "start": 74, "end": 90}, {"text": "Associated Press", "label": "organization", "start": 164, "end": 180}, {"text": "Maria Garcia", "label": "person", "start": 232, "end": 244}, {"text": "15/02/2017", "label": "date", "start": 369, "end": 379}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 37, "document_seed": 330020003, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"London": 1, "January 12, 2015": 1, "Maria Garcia": 1, "15/02/2017": 1, "Associated Press": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00038", "text": "The Guardian reports that a city council meeting in London on 16/09/2025 concluded with a unanimous vote to fund a new public transit hub. Officials said the project will address overcrowding and improve commuter safety, drawing on recent studies of urban mobility. Council member John Doe announced the allocation of £150 million, emphasizing the need for rapid implementation. Environmental advocate Maria Garcia praised the decision, noting its potential to reduce emissions and support sustainable growth. The council plans to issue construction contracts within the next quarter, pending final approvals.", "entities": [{"text": "The Guardian", "label": "organization", "start": 0, "end": 12}, {"text": "London", "label": "location", "start": 52, "end": 58}, {"text": "16/09/2025", "label": "date", "start": 62, "end": 72}, {"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 281, "end": 289}, {"text": "Maria Garcia", "label": "person", "start": 402, "end": 414}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 38, "document_seed": 1737548056, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"The Guardian": 1, "John Doe": 1, "London": 1, "16/09/2025": 1, "Maria Garcia": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00039", "text": "John Doe, a senior analyst, confirmed on 29/12/2023 that the new trade agreement will take effect next month. The Associated Press reported that negotiations were finalized after weeks of deliberations, while the BBC noted the impact on regional markets. Jane Smith, spokesperson for the commerce ministry, said the pact will enhance economic cooperation and create jobs across the sector.", "entities": [{"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 0, "end": 8}, {"text": "29/12/2023", "label": "date", "start": 41, "end": 51}, {"text": "Associated Press", "label": "organization", "start": 114, "end": 130}, {"text": "BBC", "label": "organization", "start": 213, "end": 216}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 255, "end": 265}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 39, "document_seed": 1797167079, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"John Doe": 1, "Associated Press": 1, "BBC": 1, "Jane Smith": 1, "29/12/2023": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00040", "text": "John Doe, a senior analyst at The Guardian, announced Tuesday that a new cybersecurity framework will be rolled out nationwide. The initiative, developed in partnership with several tech firms, aims to strengthen data protection ahead of upcoming regulatory changes. Jane Smith, spokesperson for the Associated Press, confirmed the rollout schedule and said the framework will be mandatory for all organizations handling personal information beginning on 23-04-2018. Officials emphasized that compliance will be monitored closely to ensure the highest standards of security across the sector.", "entities": [{"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 0, "end": 8}, {"text": "The Guardian", "label": "organization", "start": 30, "end": 42}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 267, "end": 277}, {"text": "Associated Press", "label": "organization", "start": 300, "end": 316}, {"text": "23-04-2018", "label": "date", "start": 455, "end": 465}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 40, "document_seed": 27997157, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"John Doe": 1, "The Guardian": 1, "Jane Smith": 1, "23-04-2018": 1, "Associated Press": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00041", "text": "Berlin – On 29/09/2016 the International Trade Forum released its latest market outlook, noting that consumer confidence in Asia has risen to 48,2 percent. The report, cited by economists in Tokyo, highlights a modest rebound in manufacturing output and predicts steady growth through the next quarter. Jane Smith, senior analyst at the forum, said the data underscores a shift toward sustainable demand across sectors.", "entities": [{"text": "Berlin", "label": "location", "start": 0, "end": 6}, {"text": "29/09/2016", "label": "date", "start": 12, "end": 22}, {"text": "48,2", "label": "number", "start": 142, "end": 146}, {"text": "Tokyo", "label": "location", "start": 191, "end": 196}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 303, "end": 313}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 41, "document_seed": 1993317548, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"48,2": 1, "29/09/2016": 1, "Berlin": 1, "Tokyo": 1, "Jane Smith": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00042", "text": "Tokyo announced on August 27, 2021 that its latest air‑quality index measured a particulate level of 31.5 micrograms per cubic metre, the highest reading this year. The report, compiled by the national monitoring agency, compared the data with previous measurements from London and Berlin, noting a similar upward trend in those capitals during the summer months. Officials said the spike underscores the need for immediate policy action to curb emissions and protect public health.", "entities": [{"text": "Tokyo", "label": "location", "start": 0, "end": 5}, {"text": "August 27, 2021", "label": "date", "start": 19, "end": 34}, {"text": "31.5", "label": "number", "start": 101, "end": 105}, {"text": "London", "label": "location", "start": 271, "end": 277}, {"text": "Berlin", "label": "location", "start": 282, "end": 288}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 42, "document_seed": 930719602, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Tokyo": 1, "London": 1, "31.5": 1, "Berlin": 1, "August 27, 2021": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00043", "text": "BBC reported on 19 Aug 2018 that a nationwide survey revealed a median household income of 63.3 thousand pounds, marking a modest rise from the previous year. The data, gathered by an independent research firm, showed the increase was driven primarily by higher earnings in the service sector. Jane Smith, the lead analyst on the project, said the figures suggest a slow but steady economic recovery, though she cautioned that regional disparities remain significant. The Guardian echoed the findings, noting that policymakers will need to address the underlying wage gaps to sustain growth.", "entities": [{"text": "BBC", "label": "organization", "start": 0, "end": 3}, {"text": "19 Aug 2018", "label": "date", "start": 16, "end": 27}, {"text": "63.3", "label": "number", "start": 91, "end": 95}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 294, "end": 304}, {"text": "The Guardian", "label": "organization", "start": 468, "end": 480}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 43, "document_seed": 406732790, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"BBC": 1, "19 Aug 2018": 1, "63.3": 1, "Jane Smith": 1, "The Guardian": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00044", "text": "Tokyo – On 12 Mar 2015, officials announced a new public transportation pilot aimed at reducing commuter congestion in the city centre. The scheme, coordinated by the BBC, will initially run three routes equipped with real‑time tracking technology. Jane Smith, the project manager, said the trial is expected to cut average travel times by up to 15 percent. Maria Garcia, a local resident who commutes daily, welcomed the initiative, noting that improved reliability could ease the strain on existing services.", "entities": [{"text": "Tokyo", "label": "location", "start": 0, "end": 5}, {"text": "12 Mar 2015", "label": "date", "start": 11, "end": 22}, {"text": "BBC", "label": "organization", "start": 167, "end": 170}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 249, "end": 259}, {"text": "Maria Garcia", "label": "person", "start": 358, "end": 370}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 44, "document_seed": 1483972120, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Tokyo": 1, "12 Mar 2015": 1, "Jane Smith": 1, "Maria Garcia": 1, "BBC": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00045", "text": "Reuters reported on Tuesday that a joint cultural delegation visited Tokyo to explore collaborative media projects. The delegation, led by journalist Maria Garcia, met with officials from the BBC to discuss content sharing agreements and joint reporting initiatives. Jane Smith, an analyst with the visiting team, said the talks marked a significant step toward deeper cooperation between the two broadcasters, highlighting the growing importance of cross‑border media partnerships in the region.", "entities": [{"text": "Reuters", "label": "organization", "start": 0, "end": 7}, {"text": "Tokyo", "label": "location", "start": 69, "end": 74}, {"text": "Maria Garcia", "label": "person", "start": 150, "end": 162}, {"text": "BBC", "label": "organization", "start": 192, "end": 195}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 267, "end": 277}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 45, "document_seed": 93914447, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Reuters": 1, "Maria Garcia": 1, "Tokyo": 1, "BBC": 1, "Jane Smith": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00046", "text": "The Guardian reported Tuesday that a new environmental initiative has secured funding from several private donors. Lead scientist John Doe said the program will focus on urban air quality monitoring, while senior analyst Maria Garcia highlighted the potential for community health benefits. Project coordinator Jane Smith confirmed that the first phase will launch next month, and A. Researcher contributed a peer‑reviewed study supporting the approach.", "entities": [{"text": "The Guardian", "label": "organization", "start": 0, "end": 12}, {"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 130, "end": 138}, {"text": "Maria Garcia", "label": "person", "start": 221, "end": 233}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 311, "end": 321}, {"text": "A. Researcher", "label": "person", "start": 381, "end": 394}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 46, "document_seed": 1593022413, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"The Guardian": 1, "John Doe": 1, "Maria Garcia": 1, "Jane Smith": 1, "A. Researcher": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00047", "text": "February 27, 2026 — Reuters reported today that a new public health study has found a 57,6 percent increase in vaccination rates among seniors in the Midwest. The research, led by epidemiologist Maria Garcia, attributes the rise to a recent outreach program that focused on mobile clinics and localized education campaigns. Health officials praised the results, noting that the higher uptake could significantly reduce seasonal flu hospitalizations. Jane Smith, a senior analyst at the agency, said the data underscores the effectiveness of targeted community interventions.", "entities": [{"text": "February 27, 2026", "label": "date", "start": 0, "end": 17}, {"text": "Reuters", "label": "organization", "start": 20, "end": 27}, {"text": "57,6", "label": "number", "start": 86, "end": 90}, {"text": "Maria Garcia", "label": "person", "start": 195, "end": 207}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 450, "end": 460}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 47, "document_seed": 1544523782, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"February 27, 2026": 1, "57,6": 1, "Maria Garcia": 1, "Reuters": 1, "Jane Smith": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00048", "text": "New York — The city’s housing bureau released its latest affordability report on October 28, 2020, showing the median rent for a two‑bedroom unit rose to 52.5 percent above the previous year’s level, a sharper increase than analysts anticipated. The Associated Press cited the data as a signal that rent‑control measures may need to be revisited, while Reuters highlighted the impact on low‑income households and urged policymakers to consider additional subsidies.", "entities": [{"text": "New York", "label": "location", "start": 0, "end": 8}, {"text": "October 28, 2020", "label": "date", "start": 81, "end": 97}, {"text": "52.5", "label": "number", "start": 154, "end": 158}, {"text": "Associated Press", "label": "organization", "start": 250, "end": 266}, {"text": "Reuters", "label": "organization", "start": 353, "end": 360}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 48, "document_seed": 40561083, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Associated Press": 1, "52.5": 1, "October 28, 2020": 1, "Reuters": 1, "New York": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00049", "text": "Associated Press – A joint investigation by local authorities and international partners confirmed that a previously unreported data breach affected several government agencies. The breach was discovered by cybersecurity analyst John Doe, who worked with forensic specialist Maria Garcia to contain the leak. Jane Smith, spokesperson for the Department of Defense, said the response team acted swiftly to safeguard classified information. The BBC will continue to follow the story as more details emerge.", "entities": [{"text": "Associated Press", "label": "organization", "start": 0, "end": 16}, {"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 229, "end": 237}, {"text": "Maria Garcia", "label": "person", "start": 275, "end": 287}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 309, "end": 319}, {"text": "BBC", "label": "organization", "start": 443, "end": 446}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 49, "document_seed": 1125562147, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"John Doe": 1, "Maria Garcia": 1, "Jane Smith": 1, "Associated Press": 1, "BBC": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00050", "text": "Reuters reports that on 18 Mar 2023 a major trade summit concluded with leaders signing a preliminary agreement to ease tariffs on high‑tech goods. Delegates gathered in Tokyo for the final talks, while parallel sessions were held in New York and London to discuss financial regulations. The outcomes are expected to influence global markets in the coming months, officials said.", "entities": [{"text": "Reuters", "label": "organization", "start": 0, "end": 7}, {"text": "18 Mar 2023", "label": "date", "start": 24, "end": 35}, {"text": "Tokyo", "label": "location", "start": 170, "end": 175}, {"text": "New York", "label": "location", "start": 234, "end": 242}, {"text": "London", "label": "location", "start": 247, "end": 253}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 50, "document_seed": 658704988, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Tokyo": 1, "New York": 1, "Reuters": 1, "18 Mar 2023": 1, "London": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00051", "text": "Associated Press — A joint statement released on 06-02-2015 confirmed that a new trade corridor will open between Japan and Southeast Asia, aiming to streamline logistics and boost regional commerce. The announcement was made during a press conference in Tokyo, where John Doe, senior economic advisor, outlined the expected benefits for exporters and small businesses. The BBC reported that the initiative includes provisions for digital customs clearance and shared infrastructure funding, marking a significant step toward deeper economic integration in the area.", "entities": [{"text": "Associated Press", "label": "organization", "start": 0, "end": 16}, {"text": "06-02-2015", "label": "date", "start": 49, "end": 59}, {"text": "Tokyo", "label": "location", "start": 255, "end": 260}, {"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 268, "end": 276}, {"text": "BBC", "label": "organization", "start": 374, "end": 377}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 51, "document_seed": 148529790, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Associated Press": 1, "John Doe": 1, "Tokyo": 1, "BBC": 1, "06-02-2015": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00052", "text": "Maria Garcia, a senior correspondent for The Guardian, reported from Tokyo on 29 Aug 2022 that a new public transit initiative will cut commuter times by up to fifteen minutes. The project, backed by municipal officials, integrates electric buses with existing subway lines and aims to reduce peak-hour congestion. John Doe, the city’s transport commissioner, said the plan will serve over two million passengers daily and set a model for other metropolitan areas. The announcement marks a significant step toward sustainable urban mobility in Japan’s capital.", "entities": [{"text": "Maria Garcia", "label": "person", "start": 0, "end": 12}, {"text": "The Guardian", "label": "organization", "start": 41, "end": 53}, {"text": "Tokyo", "label": "location", "start": 69, "end": 74}, {"text": "29 Aug 2022", "label": "date", "start": 78, "end": 89}, {"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 315, "end": 323}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 52, "document_seed": 1854515713, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Maria Garcia": 1, "The Guardian": 1, "29 Aug 2022": 1, "Tokyo": 1, "John Doe": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00053", "text": "June 26, 2017 — Officials announced today that a new trade agreement will be signed in a ceremony held in Berlin, marking the first such pact between the European Union and Japan in a decade. Maria Garcia, senior trade adviser to the EU delegation, said the deal will streamline customs procedures and boost bilateral investment. The agreement was negotiated over two years, with key discussions taking place in Tokyo, and will be witnessed by Jane Smith, the European Commission’s director of economic affairs.", "entities": [{"text": "June 26, 2017", "label": "date", "start": 0, "end": 13}, {"text": "Berlin", "label": "location", "start": 106, "end": 112}, {"text": "Maria Garcia", "label": "person", "start": 192, "end": 204}, {"text": "Tokyo", "label": "location", "start": 412, "end": 417}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 444, "end": 454}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 53, "document_seed": 776710271, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"June 26, 2017": 1, "Maria Garcia": 1, "Berlin": 1, "Tokyo": 1, "Jane Smith": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00054", "text": "05/05/2022 – The BBC reported that a municipal council meeting held on May 03, 2017 was revisited after newly released documents revealed the vote count had been misrecorded. The error involved a budget allocation where the figure 89.1 million dollars was entered incorrectly, prompting a re‑audit. Council member John Doe confirmed the oversight was due to a clerical slip and said the council will implement stricter verification procedures to prevent similar mistakes in future meetings.", "entities": [{"text": "05/05/2022", "label": "date", "start": 0, "end": 10}, {"text": "BBC", "label": "organization", "start": 17, "end": 20}, {"text": "May 03, 2017", "label": "date", "start": 71, "end": 83}, {"text": "89.1", "label": "number", "start": 231, "end": 235}, {"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 314, "end": 322}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 54, "document_seed": 1192900792, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"05/05/2022": 1, "John Doe": 1, "BBC": 1, "May 03, 2017": 1, "89.1": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00055", "text": "The International Monetary Fund reported today that global growth is projected to slow to 2.9 percent this year, with emerging markets facing heightened inflationary pressure. The agency highlighted that Japan's economy, centered in Tokyo, is expected to contract by 0.4 percent, while the United Kingdom, represented by London, will see a modest 0.2 percent rise. In the United States, the latest data from New York indicates a consumer confidence index of 18.1, the highest reading in a decade. The Associated Press filed this report with corroborating statements from finance ministries and central banks, emphasizing the need for coordinated policy responses to sustain recovery.", "entities": [{"text": "Tokyo", "label": "location", "start": 233, "end": 238}, {"text": "London", "label": "location", "start": 321, "end": 327}, {"text": "New York", "label": "location", "start": 408, "end": 416}, {"text": "18.1", "label": "number", "start": 458, "end": 462}, {"text": "Associated Press", "label": "organization", "start": 501, "end": 517}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 55, "document_seed": 282347033, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"New York": 1, "London": 1, "18.1": 1, "Associated Press": 1, "Tokyo": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00056", "text": "The Guardian reports that a multinational conference on climate resilience concluded in Tokyo on Tuesday, drawing attention from policymakers and environmental groups worldwide. Speakers included Maria Garcia, director of the Global Green Initiative, who outlined new carbon‑reduction targets, and John Doe, senior analyst at the International Energy Forum, who presented a forecast of regional emissions trends. In a press briefing, Japanese Minister Jane Smith emphasized the host country's commitment to achieving net‑zero emissions by 2050, urging collaborative action among nations.", "entities": [{"text": "The Guardian", "label": "organization", "start": 0, "end": 12}, {"text": "Tokyo", "label": "location", "start": 88, "end": 93}, {"text": "Maria Garcia", "label": "person", "start": 196, "end": 208}, {"text": "John Doe", "label": "person", "start": 298, "end": 306}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 452, "end": 462}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 56, "document_seed": 647503842, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"The Guardian": 1, "Maria Garcia": 1, "Jane Smith": 1, "Tokyo": 1, "John Doe": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00057", "text": "A joint economic survey released today shows that consumer confidence in major financial hubs has risen to 19,6 percent, the strongest gain in over a year. The report, compiled by analysts from both the United States and the United Kingdom, highlights that New York and London are leading the rebound, driven by robust employment figures and steadier housing markets. Maria Garcia, chief economist at the International Trade Forum, noted that the data reflects coordinated fiscal policies, while Jane Smith, senior advisor at the Global Markets Institute, warned that external shocks could still temper the upward trend.", "entities": [{"text": "19,6", "label": "number", "start": 107, "end": 111}, {"text": "New York", "label": "location", "start": 257, "end": 265}, {"text": "London", "label": "location", "start": 270, "end": 276}, {"text": "Maria Garcia", "label": "person", "start": 368, "end": 380}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 496, "end": 506}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 57, "document_seed": 1738064505, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"19,6": 1, "New York": 1, "London": 1, "Maria Garcia": 1, "Jane Smith": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00058", "text": "Berlin, 06/08/2022 – A municipal health survey released today shows that the city’s average air quality index reached 91,3, marking a modest improvement over the previous quarter. The report, compiled by the Department of Environmental Protection, attributes the gain to stricter emissions controls on diesel vehicles and expanded green zones in the city center.\n\nCity council member Jane Smith said the data validates recent policy measures and urged continued investment in public transport and renewable energy projects. She noted that while the current figure is encouraging, the target of remaining below 80 by the end of 2022 remains challenging.\n\nThe full findings will be presented at a public forum scheduled for 19-12-2022, where officials will outline next steps and seek community feedback on further initiatives.", "entities": [{"text": "Berlin", "label": "location", "start": 0, "end": 6}, {"text": "06/08/2022", "label": "date", "start": 8, "end": 18}, {"text": "91,3", "label": "number", "start": 118, "end": 122}, {"text": "Jane Smith", "label": "person", "start": 384, "end": 394}, {"text": "19-12-2022", "label": "date", "start": 722, "end": 732}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 58, "document_seed": 1558146989, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Berlin": 1, "06/08/2022": 1, "Jane Smith": 1, "91,3": 1, "19-12-2022": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00059", "text": "New York – The BBC reported on Thursday that a landmark cultural initiative will launch on 06-05-2016, aiming to expand community arts programs across the city. The project, endorsed by local officials, will feature a series of free workshops and public performances designed to engage residents of all ages. Maria Garcia, the appointed director of the initiative, said the collaboration reflects a growing commitment to accessible creative expression. The Guardian noted that the effort could serve as a model for similar programs nationwide, emphasizing the importance of sustained public investment in the arts.", "entities": [{"text": "New York", "label": "location", "start": 0, "end": 8}, {"text": "BBC", "label": "organization", "start": 15, "end": 18}, {"text": "06-05-2016", "label": "date", "start": 91, "end": 101}, {"text": "Maria Garcia", "label": "person", "start": 309, "end": 321}, {"text": "The Guardian", "label": "organization", "start": 453, "end": 465}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 59, "document_seed": 2040685559, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"BBC": 1, "Maria Garcia": 1, "06-05-2016": 1, "The Guardian": 1, "New York": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000101-00060", "text": "15 Dec 2017 – A multinational conference on renewable energy concluded today with officials highlighting the need for accelerated policy adoption. Delegates gathered in New York to review progress since the inaugural summit held on February 27, 2017, when 22,7 gigawatts of new capacity were reported across participating nations. The final communiqué, issued from London, calls for coordinated investment strategies and pledges to monitor implementation metrics over the next five years, emphasizing transparent reporting and cross‑border collaboration.", "entities": [{"text": "15 Dec 2017", "label": "date", "start": 0, "end": 11}, {"text": "New York", "label": "location", "start": 169, "end": 177}, {"text": "February 27, 2017", "label": "date", "start": 232, "end": 249}, {"text": "22,7", "label": "number", "start": 256, "end": 260}, {"text": "London", "label": "location", "start": 365, "end": 371}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 101, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "llm", "domain": "news_article", "document_type": "news_article", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b:free", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 5, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 8, "document_index": 60, "document_seed": 714384449, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "llm", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"15 Dec 2017": 1, "New York": 1, "22,7": 1, "February 27, 2017": 1, "London": 1}}}}
