{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00000", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Northwind Research.\nGuest: We measured Dr. Priya Sharma on the study dated June 13, 2016.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is 18.7 in Marcus Chen, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 48, "end": 66}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 87, "end": 103}, {"text": "June 13, 2016", "label": "date", "start": 123, "end": 136}, {"text": "18.7", "label": "number", "start": 178, "end": 182}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 186, "end": 197}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 0, "document_seed": 1959786150, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Northwind Research": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "June 13, 2016": 1, "18.7": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00001", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Elena Volkov.\nGuest: We measured Pelorus Media on the study dated James Okafor.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is 58,0 in 5.2, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 60}, {"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 81, "end": 94}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 114, "end": 126}, {"text": "58,0", "label": "number", "start": 168, "end": 172}, {"text": "5.2", "label": "number", "start": 176, "end": 179}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 1, "document_seed": 922995619, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Elena Volkov": 1, "Pelorus Media": 1, "James Okafor": 1, "58,0": 1, "5.2": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00002", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Northwind Research.\nGuest: We measured Acme Corp on the study dated Marcus Chen.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Pelorus Media in Elena Volkov, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 48, "end": 66}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 87, "end": 96}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 116, "end": 127}, {"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 169, "end": 182}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 186, "end": 198}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 2, "document_seed": 335170524, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Northwind Research": 1, "Acme Corp": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1, "Pelorus Media": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00003", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Pelorus Media.\nGuest: We measured Acme Corp on the study dated Northwind Research.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is ResearchLab in 13, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 48, "end": 61}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 82, "end": 91}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 111, "end": 129}, {"text": "ResearchLab", "label": "organization", "start": 171, "end": 182}, {"text": "13", "label": "number", "start": 186, "end": 188}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 3, "document_seed": 523640269, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Pelorus Media": 1, "Acme Corp": 1, "Northwind Research": 1, "ResearchLab": 1, "13": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00004", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Northwind Research.\nGuest: We measured Elena Volkov on the study dated Dr. Priya Sharma.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is 94.9 in Marcus Chen, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 48, "end": 66}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 87, "end": 99}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 119, "end": 135}, {"text": "94.9", "label": "number", "start": 177, "end": 181}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 185, "end": 196}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 4, "document_seed": 1641650881, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Northwind Research": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "94.9": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00005", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 65.1.\nGuest: We measured Dr. Priya Sharma on the study dated Marcus Chen.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is 7.7 in Northwind Research, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "65.1", "label": "number", "start": 48, "end": 52}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 73, "end": 89}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 109, "end": 120}, {"text": "7.7", "label": "number", "start": 162, "end": 165}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 169, "end": 187}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 5, "document_seed": 1980700424, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"65.1": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1, "7.7": 1, "Northwind Research": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00006", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Marcus Chen.\nGuest: We measured Elena Volkov on the study dated Dr. Priya Sharma.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is 05-02-2021 in James Okafor, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 59}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 80, "end": 92}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 112, "end": 128}, {"text": "05-02-2021", "label": "date", "start": 170, "end": 180}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 184, "end": 196}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 6, "document_seed": 1452258523, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Marcus Chen": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "05-02-2021": 1, "James Okafor": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00007", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at James Okafor.\nGuest: We measured 16 May 2015 on the study dated 24 Sep 2016.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is 24 Jul 2025 in December 11, 2018, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 60}, {"text": "16 May 2015", "label": "date", "start": 81, "end": 92}, {"text": "24 Sep 2016", "label": "date", "start": 112, "end": 123}, {"text": "24 Jul 2025", "label": "date", "start": 165, "end": 176}, {"text": "December 11, 2018", "label": "date", "start": 180, "end": 197}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 7, "document_seed": 509765578, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"James Okafor": 1, "16 May 2015": 1, "24 Sep 2016": 1, "24 Jul 2025": 1, "December 11, 2018": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00008", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Northwind Research.\nGuest: We measured 11,3 on the study dated Elena Volkov.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is 32,8 in Dr. Priya Sharma, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 48, "end": 66}, {"text": "11,3", "label": "number", "start": 87, "end": 91}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 111, "end": 123}, {"text": "32,8", "label": "number", "start": 165, "end": 169}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 173, "end": 189}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 8, "document_seed": 2100711671, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Northwind Research": 1, "11,3": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1, "32,8": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00009", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Dr. Priya Sharma.\nGuest: We measured Elena Volkov on the study dated 17/01/2022.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Marcus Chen in James Okafor, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 64}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 85, "end": 97}, {"text": "17/01/2022", "label": "date", "start": 117, "end": 127}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 169, "end": 180}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 184, "end": 196}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 9, "document_seed": 353192176, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1, "17/01/2022": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1, "James Okafor": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00010", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Northwind Research.\nGuest: We measured James Okafor on the study dated Dr. Priya Sharma.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is April 23, 2023 in Elena Volkov, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 48, "end": 66}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 87, "end": 99}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 119, "end": 135}, {"text": "April 23, 2023", "label": "date", "start": 177, "end": 191}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 195, "end": 207}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 10, "document_seed": 567501460, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Northwind Research": 1, "James Okafor": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "April 23, 2023": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00011", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Marcus Chen.\nGuest: We measured 11/10/2020 on the study dated 01 Mar 2015.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Pelorus Media in Acme Corp, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 59}, {"text": "11/10/2020", "label": "date", "start": 80, "end": 90}, {"text": "01 Mar 2015", "label": "date", "start": 110, "end": 121}, {"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 163, "end": 176}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 180, "end": 189}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 11, "document_seed": 955570402, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Marcus Chen": 1, "11/10/2020": 1, "01 Mar 2015": 1, "Pelorus Media": 1, "Acme Corp": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00012", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Northwind Research.\nGuest: We measured Pelorus Media on the study dated James Okafor.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Dr. Priya Sharma in Marcus Chen, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 48, "end": 66}, {"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 87, "end": 100}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 120, "end": 132}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 174, "end": 190}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 194, "end": 205}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 12, "document_seed": 106190824, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Northwind Research": 1, "Pelorus Media": 1, "James Okafor": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00013", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at James Okafor.\nGuest: We measured Elena Volkov on the study dated 23/03/2017.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Marcus Chen in Acme Corp, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 60}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 81, "end": 93}, {"text": "23/03/2017", "label": "date", "start": 113, "end": 123}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 165, "end": 176}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 180, "end": 189}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 13, "document_seed": 189232602, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"James Okafor": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1, "23/03/2017": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1, "Acme Corp": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00014", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 20-10-2017.\nGuest: We measured 64,1 on the study dated Acme Corp.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is 40.3 in Northwind Research, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "20-10-2017", "label": "date", "start": 48, "end": 58}, {"text": "64,1", "label": "number", "start": 79, "end": 83}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 103, "end": 112}, {"text": "40.3", "label": "number", "start": 154, "end": 158}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 162, "end": 180}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 14, "document_seed": 967152929, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"20-10-2017": 1, "64,1": 1, "Acme Corp": 1, "40.3": 1, "Northwind Research": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00015", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 87.9.\nGuest: We measured 16 Apr 2026 on the study dated Pelorus Media.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Northwind Research in Acme Corp, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "87.9", "label": "number", "start": 48, "end": 52}, {"text": "16 Apr 2026", "label": "date", "start": 73, "end": 84}, {"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 104, "end": 117}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 159, "end": 177}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 181, "end": 190}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 15, "document_seed": 460578371, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"87.9": 1, "16 Apr 2026": 1, "Pelorus Media": 1, "Northwind Research": 1, "Acme Corp": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00016", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Marcus Chen.\nGuest: We measured James Okafor on the study dated Pelorus Media.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Dr. Priya Sharma in 13 Sep 2019, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 59}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 80, "end": 92}, {"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 112, "end": 125}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 167, "end": 183}, {"text": "13 Sep 2019", "label": "date", "start": 187, "end": 198}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 16, "document_seed": 548202088, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Marcus Chen": 1, "James Okafor": 1, "Pelorus Media": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "13 Sep 2019": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00017", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Acme Corp.\nGuest: We measured Northwind Research on the study dated Dr. Priya Sharma.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Marcus Chen in 24/05/2017, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 48, "end": 57}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 78, "end": 96}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 116, "end": 132}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 174, "end": 185}, {"text": "24/05/2017", "label": "date", "start": 189, "end": 199}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 17, "document_seed": 1261322769, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Acme Corp": 1, "Northwind Research": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1, "24/05/2017": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00018", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 01 Aug 2019.\nGuest: We measured James Okafor on the study dated Marcus Chen.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Elena Volkov in Dr. Priya Sharma, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "01 Aug 2019", "label": "date", "start": 48, "end": 59}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 80, "end": 92}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 112, "end": 123}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 165, "end": 177}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 181, "end": 197}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 18, "document_seed": 787833291, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"01 Aug 2019": 1, "James Okafor": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00019", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 19 Dec 2020.\nGuest: We measured Dr. Priya Sharma on the study dated 32,8.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is December 07, 2017 in Acme Corp, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "19 Dec 2020", "label": "date", "start": 48, "end": 59}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 80, "end": 96}, {"text": "32,8", "label": "number", "start": 116, "end": 120}, {"text": "December 07, 2017", "label": "date", "start": 162, "end": 179}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 183, "end": 192}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 19, "document_seed": 1758545730, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"19 Dec 2020": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "32,8": 1, "December 07, 2017": 1, "Acme Corp": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00020", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at James Okafor.\nGuest: We measured Elena Volkov on the study dated 17-07-2018.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is 26.1 in Marcus Chen, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 60}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 81, "end": 93}, {"text": "17-07-2018", "label": "date", "start": 113, "end": 123}, {"text": "26.1", "label": "number", "start": 165, "end": 169}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 173, "end": 184}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 20, "document_seed": 1782572843, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"James Okafor": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1, "17-07-2018": 1, "26.1": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00021", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Dr. Priya Sharma.\nGuest: We measured Marcus Chen on the study dated Elena Volkov.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is 66,3 in James Okafor, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 64}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 85, "end": 96}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 116, "end": 128}, {"text": "66,3", "label": "number", "start": 170, "end": 174}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 178, "end": 190}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 21, "document_seed": 973131942, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1, "66,3": 1, "James Okafor": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00022", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 88,0.\nGuest: We measured Acme Corp on the study dated 17,1.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Northwind Research in 64.9, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "88,0", "label": "number", "start": 48, "end": 52}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 73, "end": 82}, {"text": "17,1", "label": "number", "start": 102, "end": 106}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 148, "end": 166}, {"text": "64.9", "label": "number", "start": 170, "end": 174}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 22, "document_seed": 1068939516, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"88,0": 1, "Acme Corp": 1, "17,1": 1, "Northwind Research": 1, "64.9": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00023", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Elena Volkov.\nGuest: We measured Dr. Priya Sharma on the study dated James Okafor.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is 81.1 in Marcus Chen, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 60}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 81, "end": 97}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 117, "end": 129}, {"text": "81.1", "label": "number", "start": 171, "end": 175}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 179, "end": 190}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 23, "document_seed": 369672387, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Elena Volkov": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "James Okafor": 1, "81.1": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00024", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Northwind Research.\nGuest: We measured Pelorus Media on the study dated Elena Volkov.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Dr. Priya Sharma in 90.1, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 48, "end": 66}, {"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 87, "end": 100}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 120, "end": 132}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 174, "end": 190}, {"text": "90.1", "label": "number", "start": 194, "end": 198}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 24, "document_seed": 1585373697, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Northwind Research": 1, "Pelorus Media": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "90.1": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00025", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 63.6.\nGuest: We measured Pelorus Media on the study dated Marcus Chen.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is 03 Dec 2015 in Acme Corp, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "63.6", "label": "number", "start": 48, "end": 52}, {"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 73, "end": 86}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 106, "end": 117}, {"text": "03 Dec 2015", "label": "date", "start": 159, "end": 170}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 174, "end": 183}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 25, "document_seed": 870030624, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"63.6": 1, "Pelorus Media": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1, "03 Dec 2015": 1, "Acme Corp": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00026", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 24/10/2026.\nGuest: We measured Pelorus Media on the study dated Northwind Research.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is 54,1 in Acme Corp, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "24/10/2026", "label": "date", "start": 48, "end": 58}, {"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 79, "end": 92}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 112, "end": 130}, {"text": "54,1", "label": "number", "start": 172, "end": 176}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 180, "end": 189}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 26, "document_seed": 938638410, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"24/10/2026": 1, "Pelorus Media": 1, "Northwind Research": 1, "54,1": 1, "Acme Corp": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00027", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at March 14, 2019.\nGuest: We measured January 08, 2022 on the study dated Elena Volkov.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Marcus Chen in 43.5, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "March 14, 2019", "label": "date", "start": 48, "end": 62}, {"text": "January 08, 2022", "label": "date", "start": 83, "end": 99}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 119, "end": 131}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 173, "end": 184}, {"text": "43.5", "label": "number", "start": 188, "end": 192}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 27, "document_seed": 2038831671, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"March 14, 2019": 1, "January 08, 2022": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1, "43.5": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00028", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 19 Apr 2015.\nGuest: We measured 92,8 on the study dated Pelorus Media.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Northwind Research in Acme Corp, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "19 Apr 2015", "label": "date", "start": 48, "end": 59}, {"text": "92,8", "label": "number", "start": 80, "end": 84}, {"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 104, "end": 117}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 159, "end": 177}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 181, "end": 190}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 28, "document_seed": 1077857410, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"19 Apr 2015": 1, "92,8": 1, "Pelorus Media": 1, "Northwind Research": 1, "Acme Corp": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00029", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Elena Volkov.\nGuest: We measured James Okafor on the study dated Dr. Priya Sharma.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Marcus Chen in A. Researcher, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 60}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 81, "end": 93}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 113, "end": 129}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 171, "end": 182}, {"text": "A. Researcher", "label": "person", "start": 186, "end": 199}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 29, "document_seed": 1208319105, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Elena Volkov": 1, "James Okafor": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1, "A. Researcher": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00030", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Dr. Priya Sharma.\nGuest: We measured Elena Volkov on the study dated 31/01/2026.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is 10,9 in Pelorus Media, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 64}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 85, "end": 97}, {"text": "31/01/2026", "label": "date", "start": 117, "end": 127}, {"text": "10,9", "label": "number", "start": 169, "end": 173}, {"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 177, "end": 190}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 30, "document_seed": 926796793, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1, "31/01/2026": 1, "10,9": 1, "Pelorus Media": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00031", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 56,8.\nGuest: We measured Elena Volkov on the study dated Northwind Research.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is James Okafor in Pelorus Media, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "56,8", "label": "number", "start": 48, "end": 52}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 73, "end": 85}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 105, "end": 123}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 165, "end": 177}, {"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 181, "end": 194}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 31, "document_seed": 1974072133, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"56,8": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1, "Northwind Research": 1, "James Okafor": 1, "Pelorus Media": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00032", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 26,4.\nGuest: We measured Marcus Chen on the study dated 12,6.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is James Okafor in Pelorus Media, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "26,4", "label": "number", "start": 48, "end": 52}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 73, "end": 84}, {"text": "12,6", "label": "number", "start": 104, "end": 108}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 150, "end": 162}, {"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 166, "end": 179}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 32, "document_seed": 829401328, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"26,4": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1, "12,6": 1, "James Okafor": 1, "Pelorus Media": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00033", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Dr. Priya Sharma.\nGuest: We measured Northwind Research on the study dated Elena Volkov.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is James Okafor in Marcus Chen, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 64}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 85, "end": 103}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 123, "end": 135}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 177, "end": 189}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 193, "end": 204}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 33, "document_seed": 1273411214, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "Northwind Research": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1, "James Okafor": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00034", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 13,6.\nGuest: We measured Northwind Research on the study dated Pelorus Media.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Marcus Chen in Acme Corp, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "13,6", "label": "number", "start": 48, "end": 52}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 73, "end": 91}, {"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 111, "end": 124}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 166, "end": 177}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 181, "end": 190}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 34, "document_seed": 177926721, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"13,6": 1, "Northwind Research": 1, "Pelorus Media": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1, "Acme Corp": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00035", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Marcus Chen.\nGuest: We measured 41,5 on the study dated Acme Corp.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is 01-08-2019 in Dr. Priya Sharma, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 59}, {"text": "41,5", "label": "number", "start": 80, "end": 84}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 104, "end": 113}, {"text": "01-08-2019", "label": "date", "start": 155, "end": 165}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 169, "end": 185}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 35, "document_seed": 2068329525, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Marcus Chen": 1, "41,5": 1, "Acme Corp": 1, "01-08-2019": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00036", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Dr. Priya Sharma.\nGuest: We measured Marcus Chen on the study dated James Okafor.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is 13.2 in Northwind Research, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 64}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 85, "end": 96}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 116, "end": 128}, {"text": "13.2", "label": "number", "start": 170, "end": 174}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 178, "end": 196}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 36, "document_seed": 625095818, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1, "James Okafor": 1, "13.2": 1, "Northwind Research": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00037", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at James Okafor.\nGuest: We measured 30 Apr 2023 on the study dated Marcus Chen.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Dr. Priya Sharma in Elena Volkov, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 60}, {"text": "30 Apr 2023", "label": "date", "start": 81, "end": 92}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 112, "end": 123}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 165, "end": 181}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 185, "end": 197}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 37, "document_seed": 563344497, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"James Okafor": 1, "30 Apr 2023": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00038", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Pelorus Media.\nGuest: We measured Dr. Priya Sharma on the study dated 40,7.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Northwind Research in April 30, 2021, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 48, "end": 61}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 82, "end": 98}, {"text": "40,7", "label": "number", "start": 118, "end": 122}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 164, "end": 182}, {"text": "April 30, 2021", "label": "date", "start": 186, "end": 200}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 38, "document_seed": 1804487981, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Pelorus Media": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "40,7": 1, "Northwind Research": 1, "April 30, 2021": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00039", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 51.1.\nGuest: We measured Pelorus Media on the study dated Acme Corp.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Northwind Research in ResearchLab, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "51.1", "label": "number", "start": 48, "end": 52}, {"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 73, "end": 86}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 106, "end": 115}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 157, "end": 175}, {"text": "ResearchLab", "label": "organization", "start": 179, "end": 190}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 39, "document_seed": 1085352625, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"51.1": 1, "Pelorus Media": 1, "Acme Corp": 1, "Northwind Research": 1, "ResearchLab": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00040", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at James Okafor.\nGuest: We measured 05-10-2026 on the study dated 18 Mar 2022.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is 27-12-2022 in 69.5, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 60}, {"text": "05-10-2026", "label": "date", "start": 81, "end": 91}, {"text": "18 Mar 2022", "label": "date", "start": 111, "end": 122}, {"text": "27-12-2022", "label": "date", "start": 164, "end": 174}, {"text": "69.5", "label": "number", "start": 178, "end": 182}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 40, "document_seed": 429396726, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"James Okafor": 1, "05-10-2026": 1, "18 Mar 2022": 1, "27-12-2022": 1, "69.5": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00041", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 08 Jul 2022.\nGuest: We measured Northwind Research on the study dated Dr. Priya Sharma.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is 04 Mar 2015 in Marcus Chen, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "08 Jul 2022", "label": "date", "start": 48, "end": 59}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 80, "end": 98}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 118, "end": 134}, {"text": "04 Mar 2015", "label": "date", "start": 176, "end": 187}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 191, "end": 202}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 41, "document_seed": 2066845070, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"08 Jul 2022": 1, "Northwind Research": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "04 Mar 2015": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00042", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Dr. Priya Sharma.\nGuest: We measured Pelorus Media on the study dated Marcus Chen.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is September 21, 2020 in Northwind Research, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility.", "entities": [{"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 64}, {"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 85, "end": 98}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 118, "end": 129}, {"text": "September 21, 2020", "label": "date", "start": 171, "end": 189}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 193, "end": 211}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 42, "document_seed": 1494947203, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "Pelorus Media": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1, "September 21, 2020": 1, "Northwind Research": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00043", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 22-05-2021.\nGuest: We measured Elena Volkov on the study dated Dr. Priya Sharma.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is James Okafor in Marcus Chen, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "22-05-2021", "label": "date", "start": 48, "end": 58}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 79, "end": 91}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 111, "end": 127}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 169, "end": 181}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 185, "end": 196}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 43, "document_seed": 415251923, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"22-05-2021": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "James Okafor": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00044", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Acme Corp.\nGuest: We measured Marcus Chen on the study dated Pelorus Media.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Northwind Research in 92,4, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 48, "end": 57}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 78, "end": 89}, {"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 109, "end": 122}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 164, "end": 182}, {"text": "92,4", "label": "number", "start": 186, "end": 190}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 44, "document_seed": 386780735, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Acme Corp": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1, "Pelorus Media": 1, "Northwind Research": 1, "92,4": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00045", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at James Okafor.\nGuest: We measured 73.5 on the study dated Elena Volkov.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Dr. Priya Sharma in Northwind Research, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 60}, {"text": "73.5", "label": "number", "start": 81, "end": 85}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 105, "end": 117}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 159, "end": 175}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 179, "end": 197}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 45, "document_seed": 1313320832, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"James Okafor": 1, "73.5": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "Northwind Research": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00046", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Acme Corp.\nGuest: We measured Pelorus Media on the study dated 24-03-2025.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is James Okafor in 11/12/2025, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 48, "end": 57}, {"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 78, "end": 91}, {"text": "24-03-2025", "label": "date", "start": 111, "end": 121}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 163, "end": 175}, {"text": "11/12/2025", "label": "date", "start": 179, "end": 189}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 46, "document_seed": 2083715049, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Acme Corp": 1, "Pelorus Media": 1, "24-03-2025": 1, "James Okafor": 1, "11/12/2025": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00047", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at December 03, 2025.\nGuest: We measured 14/05/2022 on the study dated 05-11-2018.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Elena Volkov in Dr. Priya Sharma, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "December 03, 2025", "label": "date", "start": 48, "end": 65}, {"text": "14/05/2022", "label": "date", "start": 86, "end": 96}, {"text": "05-11-2018", "label": "date", "start": 116, "end": 126}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 168, "end": 180}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 184, "end": 200}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 47, "document_seed": 533582608, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"December 03, 2025": 1, "14/05/2022": 1, "05-11-2018": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00048", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at James Okafor.\nGuest: We measured Marcus Chen on the study dated Elena Volkov.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is 08/01/2023 in 0.6, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 60}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 81, "end": 92}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 112, "end": 124}, {"text": "08/01/2023", "label": "date", "start": 166, "end": 176}, {"text": "0.6", "label": "number", "start": 180, "end": 183}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 48, "document_seed": 409284033, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"James Okafor": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1, "08/01/2023": 1, "0.6": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00049", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 8.8.\nGuest: We measured Marcus Chen on the study dated Dr. Priya Sharma.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Acme Corp in James Okafor, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "8.8", "label": "number", "start": 48, "end": 51}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 72, "end": 83}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 103, "end": 119}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 161, "end": 170}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 174, "end": 186}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 49, "document_seed": 1646354576, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"8.8": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "Acme Corp": 1, "James Okafor": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00050", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 12/12/2023.\nGuest: We measured 20.9 on the study dated 19.0.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is 62,0 in Northwind Research, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "12/12/2023", "label": "date", "start": 48, "end": 58}, {"text": "20.9", "label": "number", "start": 79, "end": 83}, {"text": "19.0", "label": "number", "start": 103, "end": 107}, {"text": "62,0", "label": "number", "start": 149, "end": 153}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 157, "end": 175}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 50, "document_seed": 1253154892, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"12/12/2023": 1, "20.9": 1, "19.0": 1, "62,0": 1, "Northwind Research": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00051", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 33.\nGuest: We measured 0.4 on the study dated Northwind Research.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is 02 Sep 2022 in James Okafor, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "33", "label": "number", "start": 48, "end": 50}, {"text": "0.4", "label": "number", "start": 71, "end": 74}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 94, "end": 112}, {"text": "02 Sep 2022", "label": "date", "start": 154, "end": 165}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 169, "end": 181}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 51, "document_seed": 85924880, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"33": 1, "0.4": 1, "Northwind Research": 1, "02 Sep 2022": 1, "James Okafor": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00052", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Northwind Research.\nGuest: We measured Dr. Priya Sharma on the study dated 69,1.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is April 07, 2015 in 04 Aug 2023, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 48, "end": 66}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 87, "end": 103}, {"text": "69,1", "label": "number", "start": 123, "end": 127}, {"text": "April 07, 2015", "label": "date", "start": 169, "end": 183}, {"text": "04 Aug 2023", "label": "date", "start": 187, "end": 198}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 52, "document_seed": 2050135525, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Northwind Research": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "69,1": 1, "April 07, 2015": 1, "04 Aug 2023": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00053", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Dr. Priya Sharma.\nGuest: We measured Pelorus Media on the study dated 28/12/2024.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is 79,8 in James Okafor, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 64}, {"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 85, "end": 98}, {"text": "28/12/2024", "label": "date", "start": 118, "end": 128}, {"text": "79,8", "label": "number", "start": 170, "end": 174}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 178, "end": 190}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 53, "document_seed": 1692459455, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "Pelorus Media": 1, "28/12/2024": 1, "79,8": 1, "James Okafor": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00054", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Pelorus Media.\nGuest: We measured 9.9 on the study dated Northwind Research.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is 80.5 in Marcus Chen, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 48, "end": 61}, {"text": "9.9", "label": "number", "start": 82, "end": 85}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 105, "end": 123}, {"text": "80.5", "label": "number", "start": 165, "end": 169}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 173, "end": 184}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 54, "document_seed": 1638155443, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Pelorus Media": 1, "9.9": 1, "Northwind Research": 1, "80.5": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00055", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Elena Volkov.\nGuest: We measured Marcus Chen on the study dated Pelorus Media.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Northwind Research in Dr. Priya Sharma, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 60}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 81, "end": 92}, {"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 112, "end": 125}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 167, "end": 185}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 189, "end": 205}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 55, "document_seed": 1907882745, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Elena Volkov": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1, "Pelorus Media": 1, "Northwind Research": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00056", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 2.10.\nGuest: We measured James Okafor on the study dated Acme Corp.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Dr. Priya Sharma in Pelorus Media, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "2.10", "label": "number", "start": 48, "end": 52}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 73, "end": 85}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 105, "end": 114}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 156, "end": 172}, {"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 176, "end": 189}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 56, "document_seed": 1124474691, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"2.10": 1, "James Okafor": 1, "Acme Corp": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "Pelorus Media": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00057", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 42,5.\nGuest: We measured 21/10/2019 on the study dated 13/11/2020.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is 18-06-2016 in Elena Volkov, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "42,5", "label": "number", "start": 48, "end": 52}, {"text": "21/10/2019", "label": "date", "start": 73, "end": 83}, {"text": "13/11/2020", "label": "date", "start": 103, "end": 113}, {"text": "18-06-2016", "label": "date", "start": 155, "end": 165}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 169, "end": 181}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 57, "document_seed": 277825873, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"42,5": 1, "21/10/2019": 1, "13/11/2020": 1, "18-06-2016": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00058", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 52.4.\nGuest: We measured Dr. Priya Sharma on the study dated Northwind Research.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Acme Corp in Pelorus Media, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "52.4", "label": "number", "start": 48, "end": 52}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 73, "end": 89}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 109, "end": 127}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 169, "end": 178}, {"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 182, "end": 195}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 58, "document_seed": 758285407, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"52.4": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "Northwind Research": 1, "Acme Corp": 1, "Pelorus Media": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00059", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Elena Volkov.\nGuest: We measured Acme Corp on the study dated James Okafor.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is 24 Oct 2016 in Dr. Priya Sharma, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 60}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 81, "end": 90}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 110, "end": 122}, {"text": "24 Oct 2016", "label": "date", "start": 164, "end": 175}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 179, "end": 195}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 59, "document_seed": 1910771218, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Elena Volkov": 1, "Acme Corp": 1, "James Okafor": 1, "24 Oct 2016": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00060", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Marcus Chen.\nGuest: We measured James Okafor on the study dated 54.8.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Northwind Research in Elena Volkov, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 59}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 80, "end": 92}, {"text": "54.8", "label": "number", "start": 112, "end": 116}, {"text": "Northwind Research", "label": "organization", "start": 158, "end": 176}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 180, "end": 192}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 60, "document_seed": 190853572, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Marcus Chen": 1, "James Okafor": 1, "54.8": 1, "Northwind Research": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00061", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at Elena Volkov.\nGuest: We measured 01/10/2020 on the study dated 07/09/2016.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is 03-03-2025 in James Okafor, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 48, "end": 60}, {"text": "01/10/2020", "label": "date", "start": 81, "end": 91}, {"text": "07/09/2016", "label": "date", "start": 111, "end": 121}, {"text": "03-03-2025", "label": "date", "start": 163, "end": 173}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 177, "end": 189}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 61, "document_seed": 1394738676, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"Elena Volkov": 1, "01/10/2020": 1, "07/09/2016": 1, "03-03-2025": 1, "James Okafor": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00062", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 83.5.\nGuest: We measured Dr. Priya Sharma on the study dated Pelorus Media.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is Marcus Chen in 36.8, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "83.5", "label": "number", "start": 48, "end": 52}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 73, "end": 89}, {"text": "Pelorus Media", "label": "organization", "start": 109, "end": 122}, {"text": "Marcus Chen", "label": "person", "start": 164, "end": 175}, {"text": "36.8", "label": "number", "start": 179, "end": 183}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 62, "document_seed": 1270530022, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"83.5": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "Pelorus Media": 1, "Marcus Chen": 1, "36.8": 1}}}}
{"id": "synthetic-00000103-00063", "text": "Host: Thanks for joining us. Our guest works at 08-09-2018.\nGuest: We measured Dr. Priya Sharma on the study dated Elena Volkov.\nHost: And headquarters for that work is James Okafor in Acme Corp, right?\n Further analysis confirms the trend across multiple runs. Ablations indicate that hyperparameters were tuned on validation data. We release code and checkpoints for reproducibility. Limitations include domain shift and label noise in weak supervision.", "entities": [{"text": "08-09-2018", "label": "date", "start": 48, "end": 58}, {"text": "Dr. Priya Sharma", "label": "person", "start": 79, "end": 95}, {"text": "Elena Volkov", "label": "person", "start": 115, "end": 127}, {"text": "James Okafor", "label": "person", "start": 169, "end": 181}, {"text": "Acme Corp", "label": "organization", "start": 185, "end": 194}], "source": "synthetic", "gold_source": "synthetic", "synthetic_meta": {"seed": 103, "num_documents": 100, "engine": "procedural", "domain": "transcript", "document_type": "transcript", "text_length": {"min_chars": 200, "max_chars": 800}, "llm_model": "", "llm_agent_mode": "per_doc", "llm_parallelism": 3, "llm_provider_max_attempts": 3, "llm_validation_max_attempts": 3, "document_index": 63, "document_seed": 43223124, "planned_entity_count": 5, "text_engine": "procedural", "entity_usage": {"planned": 5, "used_exactly_once": 5, "missing": [], "duplicate_in_text": [], "occurrence_counts": {"08-09-2018": 1, "Dr. Priya Sharma": 1, "Elena Volkov": 1, "James Okafor": 1, "Acme Corp": 1}}}}
